{\clip(190,219,190,219)\t(0,600,\clip(100,217,280,220))\t(16600,17100,\clip(190,217,190,220))}m 0 0 m 180 1 l 0 1 l 0 0 l 180 0
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}翻\h译
王子鱼\h\h\hCriticalHit\h\h\h白小问\h\h\h远离风暴浩劫\h\h\h梦回江南ny
有鹿er\h\h\hmojoonx\h\h\h锅锅奶奶\h\h\h汤包小螺螺\h\h\hKenun
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}校对\h&\h后期
homosapiens\h\h\h\h你以为列
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}总监
-=大红=-
片头推广合作洽谈\h请联系普罗米修斯邮箱\hPLMXS2016@GmaiL.com
我和我老伴辛辛苦苦攒下的家当
My husband and I worked for everything I had.
离我远点
Don't come near me!
行  好的
Okay, okay.
好了  你不想这样做
Okay. Hey, you don't wanna do this.
我不知道自己怎么就这么蠢
I don't know how I could be so stupid!
等等  把手给我
Hey, hold on a second. Give me your hand.
我什么都没了  都没了
I have nothing! Nothing!
你当然还有
Sure, you do.
费尔德曼太太  要不你向我靠近一步
Mrs. Feldman, how about you take a step towards me?
我们进来说
We'll go inside and talk.
请马上派危机应对单位过来
I need a Crisis Response Unit here right now.
赶紧让直升机离开这里  不  不要
Get that chopper out of here! No, no, no, no!
葛蕾丝的坠落
早安  小熊
Hey, bear.
早安  宝贝
Hey, baby.
你得起床了
You gotta get up.
我知道
I know.
下雨了吗
Is that rain?
对  差不多一小时前就停了
Yeah, it stopped about an hour ago.
顺便说一下  钥匙我给你放桌上了
I left the keys on the table for you, by the way.
亲爱的  今天是周二
Baby, it's Tuesday.
周二你要带你妈妈去杂货店
You take your mom to the grocery store on Tuesdays.
不用
Nah, it's...
没事的  我告诉过她我今晚晚点去看她
...it's fine. I told her I'd come by later tonight, and...
我只想在家待着
I just need to stay in.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
-没事  -你怎么了
- Yeah. - What's wrong?
没事  没什么
No, no, nothing. Nothing's wrong.
一切都好
Nothing's wrong.
你把车开走吧
Take the car.
起床了
Now, get up.
好吧  像以前一样  你晚点再告诉我
Okay, well, you'll tell me later, like you always do.
我等着
I'll wait.
-好吗  -好的
- All right? - Okay.
现在我们来说说葛蕾丝·沃特斯的案子
Now we're going to move over to the Grace Waters case.
大家都在讨论这个案子
Everyone's talking about it.
据称  该名女子谋杀了她的丈夫
The woman killed her husband, allegedly.
等等  我们必须"据称"
Hold on, now. Yes, we must say "allegedly."
本地人口不足十万人
We have a population of less than 100,000.
之前从未发生过这种事
Nothing like this has ever happened before--
不过你看过地方检察官的报告了吗
But have you seen the reports from the DA?
很明显  绝对是她干的
It's clear. She totally did it.
茉莉
Jasmine.
来了
Coming.
给  你的下一个案子
Here. Your next case.
葛蕾丝·沃特斯吗  这案子我接不了
Grace Waters? I can't do this.
你能接  你也要接
Yeah, you can, and you will.
她想认罪  所以案子很简单
She wants to plead guilty, so this is completely easy.
去跟她还有地方检察官谈谈
Go talk to her, talk to the DA,
商量好条件  让她认罪
get it worked out, get the plea done.
这是个备受关注的案子
It's really high-profile,
我们不能处理不当或是去庭审
and we don't need it mishandled or going to trial.
要不把这个案子交给提尔萨或者唐尼吧
What about giving it to Tilsa or Donnie?
他们其实
I mean, they are more...
-更能胜任  -就你来办
- equipped to do this - You are doing it.
我们谈过多少次了
We go through this all the time.
你没问题  认罪协议是你的专长
You can do it. Plea deals are your specialty.
她坚持认罪
She's adamant about pleading guilty.
大量的证据都指向她
There's an overwhelming mountain of evidence against her.
这案子简直易如反掌  把它搞定就好
This is open-and-shut. Just go get it done.
我希望这周内办妥  好打发走那帮媒体
I want it done this week so this media circus will go away.
-谢谢  -但是罗里  我
- Thank you. - But, Rory, I...
去吧
Go.
好的
Okay.
你能相信吗
Can you believe this?
恭喜  你知道我们都想接这个案子
Ah! Congratulations, girl. You know we all wanted it.
我真不敢相信他居然把案子给你了
I cannot believe he gave it to you.
-唐尼  闭嘴  -我不明白
- Donnie, shut the hell up. - I don't understand.
好的  但谁问你了  真不分场合
OK. But who asked you? It's not the time.
没什么好庆祝的  提尔萨
This is nothing to celebrate, Tilsa.
听着  这可是大案子
Look, it's a big case,
你和地方检察官的关系很好吧
but you have a great relationship with the DA, right?
或许这才最符合她的利益
So maybe that's in her best interest.
呵呵
Great.
我和地方检察官的关系很好
I have a great relationship with the DA.
那太好了
That's awesome.
不管怎样  这真令人难过  看看周围
Either way, it's really sad. Look around.
所有人都在谈论这事
And I don't see any way out of it.
要我说  情况变得更糟了
If you ask me, it's getting worse.
我敢说  全镇都在议论这事
I can tell you, without a doubt, the whole town's talking.
我今早买咖啡时
This morning, while I was getting coffee,
听到人们都在谈论葛蕾丝·沃特斯的案子
two or three conversations, all about the Grace Waters case.
很有趣  下一位听众怎么看
Well, that's interesting. How about our next caller?
我觉得她肯定有罪
I mean, I feel like she's totally guilty.
我都不明白我们为什么要浪费钱来审判她
I don't even know why we are wasting money with a trial.
直接把她捆在电椅上  按下开关
Just tie her up to an electric chair, and hit the switch.
嘭的一声  问题就解决了
Boom! Problem solved.
我们正在霍洛威拘留所外
We're outside the Holloway Correctional Facility,
葛蕾丝·沃特斯现在被关押在这里
where Grace Waters is being held.
她将在三天后出庭
She's scheduled for court in three days.
众所周知
As many of you know,
她被指控谋杀了她的丈夫
she's been accused of murdering her husband.
止步  非请勿进
你好  我是公设辩护人办公室的
Hi, I'm Jasmine Bryant
茉莉·布莱恩特
from the public defender's office.
我来找葛蕾丝·沃特斯
I'm here for Grace Waters.
好的女士  请过一下这里
Yes, ma'am. Step through here for me, please.
请把包放在桌上
And just put your bag on the table for me.
好的
Okay.
-好了  -好的
- All right. - Okay.
坐吧  我一会就带她来
Just have a seat, and I will be right back with her.
不好意思
-E-Excuse me.
-什么事  -我有什么需要注意的吗
- Yes? - Um, is there anything I should know?
这是你的第一个杀人犯吗
Is this your first murderer?
是的
Yeah.
什么都不用担心  她会被拷上的
You don't have anything to worry about. She'll be shackled.
把双手放在桌上
Put your hands on the desk for me.
我是你的律师  我叫茉莉·布莱恩特
I'm your attorney, Jasmine Bryant.
我是公设辩护人办公室的
I'm from the public defender's office.
是法院指派我来的
I was appointed by the court.
我告诉过他们我不要律师
I told them I didn't want a lawyer.
就算不是我  也会有别的律师来
Well, if not me, then some other lawyer will be here.
法官对此很清楚
The judge was very clear on that.
我了解到你打算认罪  对吗
So, I understand that you want to plead guilty?
你多大了
How old are you?
二十六
Twenty-six.
你是哪个学校毕业的
What school did you go to?
鲁斯顿
Ruston.
社区大学
Community college.
然后我去了班尼威尔法律大学
And then I went on to Baniview Law.
你的资料
Your file... um...
我在来这里的路上稍微看了一下
I had a chance to glance at it on my way over here,
我有点不明白  你曾在银行工作
and, um, I'm a little confused. You worked at a bank,
你连交通规则都没违反过  但你却杀人
you've never even had a traffic violation, and now you're here.
我打算向地方检察官申请
I'm gonna ask the DA for 15 years
十五年监禁并允许假释
with the possibility of parole.
我也许可以说服他
I may be able to sell that to him.
你信天主教
You're Catholic.
-对  -我不是在问你
- Yes. - That wasn't a question.
我看到念珠了
I see the rosary.
你是天主教徒吗
Are you Catholic?
以圣父
In the name of the Father,
圣子
and the Son,
圣灵的名义
and the Holy Spirit...
那你会念《圣母圣咏》吗
So, you pray the rosary?
会
Yes.
我想转到这附近的监狱
I want to move to a prison close to here.
我想有机会看一下我的儿子
I want to be able to see my son and my grandbaby...
和小孙子
at some point.
我想把这些
And I want that
加进认罪协议
in the plea deal.
好的  我想想办法
Okay. I'll see what I can do.
警卫
Guard!
好了  她是什么样的人
Okay. So what was she like?
和我想的完全不一样
Well, it was nothing like I expected.
她就像你和我的妈妈一样
She was like my mom, and yours.
她很  温柔
She was...gentle.
温柔
Gentle.
但乍一看
You know, but, at first glance...
她就是个完美的被告
she appears to be a picture-perfect defendant.
她给孩子们烤饼干
She baked cookies for kids,
在教堂唱诗班唱歌  在主日学校教书
she sang in a church choir, she taught Sunday school.
好多材料你都可以用来帮她辩护
There's a lot of good things here for you to build a solid defense.
有大量的证据指向她是杀人犯
The evidence against her is overwhelming.
但能超越合理怀疑吗  这只是间接证据
But beyond a reasonable doubt? It was circumstantial.
指判决被告有罪时陪审员不会对证据有合理怀疑
她承认是她干的  她想认罪
She confessed she did it. She wants to plead guilty.
我是说
I mean...
-这个  -唐尼  冷静
- This - Donnie, just chill.
不  不  别拦着他
No, no, no. No, no.
你想说什么  唐尼
What, Donnie?
我不是看轻你作为公共辩护律师的
I-I-I'm not trying to take away from your remarkable ability
出众才能
as a public defender,
但他们给你这个案子是为了让你帮她认罪
um, but they gave you this case because they want you to plead it,
把事情办妥
be done with it,
以免让公设辩护人办公室难堪
as to not embarrass the public defender's office.
但是这案子如此备受关注
But how embarrassing would it be,
如果你遗漏了什么
due to the high profile of this case,
那会有多尴尬
if you were missing something?
我会遗漏什么  唐尼
What could I be missing, Donnie?
对  正如她所说  她还能遗漏什么
Okay, like she said, okay, what could she be missing?
那个女人认罪了  不是吗
The woman confessed, right?
-没错  -请不要怂恿她
- Exactly. - Please don't encourage her.
她向你认罪了吗
Did she confess to you?
-没有  她告诉警官她  -明白了吗
-No, she told the officers that she - Ah. You see?
明白了吗  这就是我说的
You see? This is what I'm talkin' about.
你不能在不了解事实的情况下就定她的罪
You can't just plea her down without knowing all of the facts.
我了解事实  好吗
I know the facts, okay?
这个案子一目了然  唐尼
This is an open-and-shut, Donnie.
以我们的工作量  我们没有足够的时间
With our workload, we don't have enough time or money
或金钱来仔细了解这个案子
to even deal with this.
该死  我们代理的那些毒贩都比我们有钱
Hell, the drug dealers we represent make more money than us,
他们对我们也没有丝毫尊重
and they have no respect for us.
听着  我不想和你吵
Look, I'm not gonna go back and forth with you.
-对不起   -你总是这个样子
- Sorry, - You always do this.
这和一个为邻居孩子烤饼干的
but what does that have to do with the Sunday school teacher
主日学校的老师有什么关系呢
who bakes cookies for kids in the neighborhood?
好吧  我觉得我们该走了
Okay,so I think we should leave.
这是你这一整晚说的最明智的话
You know, that is the most sensible thing you've said all night.
谢谢
Thank you.
我永远不会习惯
You know, I will never get used to seeing
看到人们进监狱
people going to jail.
无论这是否是你的案子
Either this is your cause, or it ain't.
好好想想  小茉
Figure it out, Jas.
-再见乔丹  -晚安  姐妹
- Jordan. - Night, girl.
那我们明天见
So we'll see you tomorrow.
-好的  -好吗  祝你们今晚愉快
- Yeah. - Okay, y'all have a nice night.
-感谢你请我们来  -你也是  提尔萨
- Thanks for having us. - You, too, Tilsa.
家里很漂亮  我会跟他聊聊的  好吗
Beautiful home. I'mma talk to him, okay?
-不用麻烦了  -就小聊一下
- Don't worry about it. - Just a little chat.
唐尼  你给我过来
Donnie, get your ass over here!
这就是他们不再邀请我们来的原因
This is why they don't invite us no more.
你现在的行为
How you actin' right now...
-懂我意思了吧  -是
- See what I mean? - Yeah.
赢不了
Can't win.
我看到一个老太太坠楼死了
I saw an old woman fall to her death.
不过我没事
But I'm all right.
到你说了
Your turn.
我刚从法学院毕业的时候
You know, when I graduated from law school...
我感觉像中了彩票一样
I thought I had hit the lottery.
是啊
Yeah.
但是现在我身处这个行业  我
But now that I'm into it, I...
这些人
These people
是杀人犯
are murderers
骗子
and liars.
还有小偷
And they're thieves, babe.
为他们辩护  我
And to defend them, I...
我只是在重新考虑这一切
I'm just having second thoughts about all of this.
真的
Really.
我只是想在那里待到
I just wanna stay there long enough
还完学生贷款
so I can get these student loans paid off.
我再也不想当律师了
I don't want to be a lawyer anymore.
别这么说
No, come on.
我不想
I don't.
过来
Oh, come on.
我不想
I don't.
这是你注定要做的事
This is what you're meant to do.
你知道的  宝贝  过来
You know that, babe. Come on.
昨晚我可能喝多了点  我的错
Last night I may have had one too many. My bad.
那个算道歉吗
Was that an apology?
你说是就是
If that's what you call it.
我认为你做得太棒了  茉莉
Well, I think you do a great job, Jasmine.
谢谢  提尔萨
Thanks, Tilsa.
大概在七点半
At about 7:30.
你什么时候去跟地方检察官谈
When are you talking to, uh,
有关葛蕾丝·沃特斯的案子
the DA about Grace Waters?
-今天下午晚些时候  -做好就行
- Uh, later this afternoon. - Get it done,
-把事情做好  -我会去法院见他
- get it done, get it done. - I'm meeting him at court.
茉莉
Jasmine.
有个马尔科姆·华特斯找你
There's a Malcolm Waters here to see you.
那是谁
Who's that?
-我不知道  -他预约了吗
- I don't know. - Is he in the appointment book?
行  好吧
Okay, all right.
马尔科姆吗
Malcolm?
是我  你是茉莉吗
Yes, are you Jasmine?
是的  你好
Yes, hi.
葛蕾丝·沃特斯是我母亲
Grace Waters is my mother.
你会帮她的  对吗
You're gonna help her, right?
求你了
Uh, please.
我爱我母亲  我知道她是清白的  我知道
I love my mother, and I know she's innocent. I know she is.
她不可能对任何人那么做  不会的
She couldn't do that to anyone. No one.
我小时候她甚至不忍心杀蜘蛛
She wouldn't even kill spiders when I was growing up.
她让我爸用杯子把它们放出去
She'd make my dad take 'em outside in a cup.
你得帮帮她
You have to help her.
她想认罪
She wants to plead guilty.
不  不要让她这么做  求你了
No, no, no, don't let her do that, please.
我要能跟她说上话就好了  她不肯见我
If I could talk to her. She won't see me.
你得帮帮她  或者让我进去见见她
You have to help her or get me in to see her.
你不能让她认罪
You can't let her plead guilty.
很抱歉  我帮不了你
I'm sorry, there's nothing I can do.
她想认罪
She wants to plead.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
我要她终生监禁  不得假释
I want life without parole.
你认真的吗
Look, are you serious?
她没有犯罪记录  是个模范公民
She has no record. She's a model citizen.
她没有前科
She has no priors.
拜托  我们要求判十五年
Come on, we want 15 years.
想都别想
No deal.
她想认罪  就得重判
She wants a plea, she gets the max.
那让她去米尔斯通监狱如何
Well, what about giving her Millstone Prison,
-这样她能离她儿子近点  -这个我会考虑
- so she'll be closer to her son? - That I'll consider.
他们要求判最重刑
They're offering the maximum,
终生监禁  不得假释
life without the possibility of parole.
-那就是他们最好的条件了吗  -他很坚决
- And that's the best they can do? - He's adamant about it.
如果我们上庭审判  他可能主张死刑
If we went to trial, he could ask for the death penalty.
我觉得你该接受这个条件
I think you should take this deal.
好吧
Okay.
好吗
Okay?
好吧  我接受
Okay, do it.
喂
Yes?
你好  萨拉小姐
Hi, Miss Sarah?
是我
Yes?
我是茉莉·布莱恩特
This is Jasmine Bryant.
我是葛蕾丝·沃特斯的辩护律师
I'm representing Grace Waters.
我今早能过来拜访一下吗
Is it possible that I could come by this morning?
当然可以  我在家
Well, yes, I'm home.
我的地址是西课巷2342号
My address is 2342 West Lesson Lane.
-好的  谢谢你  -不客气
- Okay. Thank you. - All right.
待会见
See you then.
你好
Hi.
你好  你能帮我一把吗
Hi, uh, would you mind, please?
-当然  -这个太重了
- Oh, sure. - This thing is so heavy.
-没问题  -我的天
- No problem. - Oh, my goodness.
我有三个租户
I got three tenants.
把这个拉到路边就好
Just get it on this curb, and we'll be fine.
好的
Okay.
谢谢你  非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you so much.
没事
Okay.
那位  那位是
Oh, yeah, that's, uh--
那是我的一个租户
That's one of my tenants, there.
他们没有家人  真可怜
They don't have family. It's sad.
进来吧  亲爱的
But come on in, honey.
-进来躲躲雨  -好的
- Come in out of this rain. - Okay.
你喝咖啡吗
Do you like coffee?
-我喝  谢谢你  -不用谢
- Oh, I do. Thank you very much. - All right.
预报说今天会是晴天
They said there would be sunshine today.
他们也就这水平了
So much for what they know.
从来都不准  对吧  我就知道
I know, right? I know.
那么
So...
你来见我所为何事
...what brings you to see me?
眼泪
Tears.
我昨天看见葛蕾丝女士哭了
I saw Miss Grace cry tears
我从来没见过罪犯哭成那样
that I've never seen a guilty person cry yesterday.
我得承认  我觉得很难受
You know, I have to tell you, I feel really bad.
这很大程度是我的错
A lot of this is my fault.
你为什么这么说
Why do you say that?
年纪是个贱人  亲爱的  它会悄悄靠近你
Age is a bitch, darling. It'll sneak up on you.
头一天还貌美如花  就像你  青春可爱
One day you all lovely-lookin', just like you, all young and lovely.
第二天就到了我这个年纪
Seem like the next day you're my age,
思索着时间都去哪了
wondering where all the time went.
我比她大一点
I'm a little older than she is.
但我不想她像我一样
But I didn't want her to be like me.
独自一人
Lonely...
跟一群老太婆和她们的猫一起
and livin' in a house
住一栋房子里
with old ladies and their cats.
她心地那么善良
She's such a good soul.
所以我鼓励她走出去
So, I tried to encourage her to go out,
我总是鼓励她  但是
you know, all the time, but...
她不肯
she wouldn't do it.
谢谢
Thank you.
不用谢  之后她儿子结婚了
You're welcome. And then, when her, uh, son got married...
那时一切都发生了转变
...that's when everything took a turn.
我亲眼看到她变了个人
I mean, I literally watched as she changed before my very eyes.
那是在婚礼后
It was after the wedding.
我们坐一起品酒聊天
We were sitting and talking over a glass of wine, and...
她为自己的生活在想象和现实中的巨大差异
Oh, she was so sad about what she thought her life would be,
而感到难过
and... and what it was.
实际并没有很差
And it wasn't bad.
因为她有一个漂亮的家
No, 'cause she had a lovely home. Beautiful home.
还有一份好工作
And a good job, too.
但她的前夫
But her ex-husband,
过得比她更好
he was living better than she was, and...
他的现在妻子过着葛蕾丝梦寐以求的生活
seemed like his wife was living Grace's dream, and--
你要记下来吗
You gonna take notes?
对啊  谢谢
Oh. Yes. Uh, thank you.
好了
Yes.
所以  婚礼过后
So, it was after the wedding,
我们刚回来  还没来得及脱下礼服
and we had come in. We hadn't even taken off our dresses,
她就  她就彻底崩溃了
when she started to just-- just come apart at the seams.
婚礼在她前夫家举办的
I mean, that wedding took place in her ex-husband's house,
那里曾经是葛蕾丝家
and that used to be Grace's house.
我搞不懂  葛蕾丝
I don't know, Grace,
他们为什么非得在那个房子里举办婚礼
why'd they have to have a wedding in the house?
还有那些俗气的帘子
And those tacky drapes.
等等  那些曾经是我的帘子
Wait, now, those were my drapes.
谢谢
Thank you.
他甚至没换掉那些帘子吗
He didn't even change the drapes?
他甚至没换掉那些帘子
He didn't even change the drapes.
我们曾在那房子里共建过一段人生
We built a life in that house.
而我现在却在这里  只是
And here I am, just...
很愤怒
Angry.
不  我不是真的生气  我只是很受伤
No, I'm not really angry. I'm just hurt.
还有很愤怒  承认吧
And angry. Go on, say it.
好吧
Okay.
好吧  我很愤怒
Okay, I am angry.
这就对了
Damn right.
你完全有权利生气
And you have every right, so be pissed.
见鬼了
Hell.
那个小贱人的年纪都可以做他女儿了
That little heifer's young enough to be his daughter.
是吧
Right?
她就比我儿子大五岁
She is five years older than my son.
我们的儿子
Our son.
就这么不公平
Just so unfair.
他就这么继续过他的人生
It's like he just went on with his life.
我就像是个会拖累他的包袱一样
Like I was some kind of speed bump that just slowed him down.
只是
Just...
我是怎么沦落到这个地步的
How did I even get here?
我想要回我的生活
I want my life back.
我想要回我的青春
I want my youth back.
我想开怀大笑
I want to laugh.
我想爱上一个人  我想
I wanna love somebody, I wanna...
被爱
be loved.
你青春的事我帮不上忙
I can't help you with your youth,
但是剩下的我倒能搭把手
but I can help you with the rest of it.
你得从这房子里出去  去约会
You need to get the hell out this house and meet somebody.
和谁
Who?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是我看到电视上的广告
But I see these commercials on TV.
你可以上基督徒在线约会网
You could go on ChristianDateOnline.Com.
什么
What?
-你可以试试  -我才不试
- You could! - No, I could not.
我拒绝  得了吧  萨拉
No. Come on, now, Sarah.
得了吧  如果我想和某人约会  我希望
No, come on. If I wanted to meet someone, I want to do it...
我希望用传统的方式
I want to do it the old-fashioned way.
以传统的方式来看现在可都是深夜了
Might be a little late in the evening for the old-fashioned way.
那他们是怎么遇上的
So how'd the two meet?
在一个美术馆
At an art gallery.
等等
Hold on.
让我找找
Let me see.
你好呀
Hi there. Oh...
这是他们收回她房子时遗落的传单
This is a flyer from when they repossessed her house.
他们把她所有东西都扔到街上
They put everything out on the street,
我尽可能地帮她收了一些东西
and I gathered those things that I could, at least the things
一些至少我认为对她很珍贵的东西
I thought that would be of value to her.
这是他在那个美术馆的展览宣传单
This is a flyer from his show
她就是在那里遇见他的
at that gallery where she met him.
这是他的相片
That's his photograph.
他遇到她第二天就把原片给了她
He gave her the original the day after he met her.
他是名摄影师
He was a photographer.
你留着吧
You can keep that.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我真想再多跟你聊会
I'd love to talk to you some more,
但我的租客们还没吃早饭
but my ladies haven't had their breakfast.
我们可以以后再聊吗
Would you mind if we talked again later?
好的  没问题
Oh, okay. Um, sure. Um...
谢谢  谢谢你让我过来
Thank you. Thank you so much for having me.
不  谢谢你能来
No, thank you for coming.
没事的  来吧
That's nothing, come on.
谢谢你这么关心葛蕾丝  多保重
Uh, thank you for caring so much about Grace and taking good care.
好的  太谢谢你了
All right, thank you so much.
-不客气  -祝您今日愉快
- All right. - Have a great day.
-谢谢  再见  -好的  再见
- Thank you. Buh-bye. - Okay, bye-bye.
我回来了  宝贝
Hey, babe.
快来  看看这个
Come here, look at this.
能不能先来个亲亲问候一下
Can I get a hello first? Can I get some love?
来看看这个  告诉我你看到了什么
Okay. Now, look at this and tell me what you see.
-是鲁米诺  -是的
- Uh... that's luminol. - Yes.
用于检测犯罪现场肉眼无法观察到的血液
这里也有很多血
It's a lot of blood, too.
有一些地方颜色很深而另一些地方浅一些
And it's dark in some places and lighter in the others.
对  然后呢
Yeah, and?
假设他因为头部被击打
And if he lost this much blood,
流了很多血
say, from a blow to the head,
为什么在照片里看起来
why is it pooling from the outside in,
像是从外部流成一滩呢
as it looks like it did in the picture? Hmm?
我觉得你正在问一些优秀律师才会问的问题
Then I'd say that you're asking the questions a good lawyer would.
罗里  你好
Rory, hi.
请给我来杯咖啡  什么事
Some coffee in here, please. Yeah?
我想给你看看这个
Um, yeah, I wanted you to see this.
你看这些血液是如何从外部汇集进来的
You see how the blood is pooling from the outside in?
-是嘛  -我想请一位血液喷溅
- Yeah. - I wanna hire an expert in blood splatter
和痕量血迹鉴定方面的专家
and in luminol--
你这九个月白来了吗
Where have you been for the past nine months?
我们请不起血迹鉴定专家
This office cannot afford a blood pattern expert.
你在说什么鬼话  再说请专家干什么
What you talking about? What's this about anyway?
葛蕾丝·沃特斯  她的辩词
Grace Waters, her defense.
那女人已经认罪了
That woman is pleading guilty.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
现在去一趟监狱  让她把认罪协议签了
Now, get down to the jail and get the plea deal signed.
就在那儿  让她把它签了
It's already there. Get it signed.
这场闹剧该结束了  我的电话响个不停
This circus needs to stop. My phone's ringing off the hook.
包括市长在内的所有人都为了这事打给我
I've got the mayor and everybody calling me about this.
罗里  但我发现了一些很重要的事情  我觉得
Rory, but I found some really great stuff, and I think--
茉莉
Jasmine.
如果你在法庭上也如此争辩的话
If you argued like this in court,
你倒是真能成为一名律师
you could actually be a lawyer.
去吧
Go.
咖啡  咖啡  咖啡
Coffee! Coffee! Coffee!
-很抱歉  -谢谢
- So sorry. - Thank you.
这是什么鬼玩意儿
What the hell is this?
霍洛威看守所
访客停车场
这是地方检察官开具的认罪协议
This is the plea agreement from the DA.
他说会把你安排在你儿子
He did manage to say that he will put you in a facility
住所附近的监狱里
that's close to your son.
就签在这里
You can sign here.
你有笔吗
You have a pen?
有  抱歉
Yeah. Sorry.
你去找过谁了
Who've you been talkin' to?
你的朋友  萨拉
Your friend Sarah.
葛蕾丝  请告诉我到底发生了什么
Grace, please tell me what happened.
他对你做了什么
What did he do to you?
求你了
Please.
告诉我
Tell me.
高跟鞋
Heels.
我不知道为什么我会记得那天的高跟鞋
I don't know why I remember the heels that day.
那是很平常的一天  再平常不过了
It was a normal day, like any other.
当我醒来时
When you wake up...
却不知道
you don't know that...
那一天将会是改变我人生的一天
today will be the day to change your life...
就这么完了
End it.
一切都是那么平常
Everything felt so normal.
谢谢
Thank you.
去看吧
-萨拉
那天下班后  我去了一家画廊的开幕式
After work that day, I went to a... a gallery opening.
虽然有点累
I was a little tired,
但我还是想去看看萨拉说的这个展览
but I wanted to see this exhibit that Sarah had told me about.
她担心我在屋里待太久
She was worried about me being in the house too much.
坚持要我去  所以
But she was adamant that I go, so...
我去了
I did.
-你好  -请原谅  不好意思
- Hi. - Excuse me. I'm sorry.
我知道
Ah... I get it,
你得在合适的灯光下看这些照片
you have to see these in the right light.
而这里最好的灯光
And the best lighting in the room is...
就在这里  所以
right here, so...
这展览的主人是我的世交
The owner's a family friend,
我没勇气告诉她这里的灯光很糟
and I don't have the heart to tell her that the lighting sucks.
其实从这里看也没有那么糟
Well, it's not really that bad from right here.
你对光和阴影很了解吗
And what do you know about shadows and light?
我什么都不了解  包括这位摄影师
I don't know anything as well as this photographer.
她很有才华
She's... brilliant.
你为什么那么肯定她是名女性
What makes you so sure that she's a she?
看名字
The name.
香农
Shannon.
再看那些阴影
And look at the shadows,
还有她拍摄这些部落族人情感的方式
the way she captures the emotions of these tribes.
只有在女人眼里才是这样  太美了
Now, only a woman sees like that. It's beautiful.
我觉得她也是埃塞俄比亚人
You know what? I think she's Ethiopian, too,
因为她得认识人才能进部落
because she has to know somebody to get in
才能去了解这些人
and get to know these people.
有些地区非常偏远
Some of these places are extremely remote.
我觉得只有当地人才能如此地靠近
I think only a native can navigate this closely.
看来你很了解埃塞俄比亚
You seem to know a lot about Ethiopia.
都是从书上读到的
Just what I've read.
我爱非洲
I love Africa.
非洲的历史
African history.
真想有天能去看看
I wanna go one day.
你该去  那会改变你的一生
You should. It'll change your life.
你去过吗
Oh, you've been?
-去过  -你真幸运
- I have. - Lucky you.
遇见你  也很幸运
Lucky me, to meet you.
天啊  那是
Ooh, wow, is that a...
-那是乌佐项链吗  -是的  好眼力
- Is that an Uzo necklace? - Yeah, good eye.
在非洲买的  很特别吧
Got this in Africa. One of a kind.
真漂亮
Beautiful.
我们需要你
We need you.
不好意思  我要带这位帅哥离开一下
Excuse me while I take this handsome thing away.
-拜托了  -当然可以
- Please. - Absolutely.
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
非常感谢大家来这个展览
thank you so much for coming to this exhibit.
令人激动的是这位杰出的艺术家就在这里
We are so excited to have this amazing artist here.
我们都很喜爱他在霍洛威展出的这些作品
We love his work here in Holloway.
女士们先生们  隆重介绍  香农·德隆
Introducing Shannon Delong, ladies and gentlemen.
女士们先生们  非常感谢各位今晚的莅临
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you so much for coming out tonight.
我衷心地感谢
I really appreciate that.
我想和不太了解我的人说
Um, for those of you that don't know me,
我是个内向的人
I am an introvert,
所以我不擅长在很多人面前
which means I have trouble speaking in front of...
发言
semi-large crowds.
但我希望你们能喜欢这个展览
But I hope you enjoy the exhibit.
它的名字叫"古佐"
It's called "Guzo."
源自我的埃塞俄比亚之旅
It is from my travels in Ethiopia.
记住
And remember...
今晚的大部分收入都将捐给慈善机构
a lot of the proceeds tonight go to charity, so...
所以请多多消费
please spend a large amount of money.
-了解  了解  -好吗  谢谢
- Hear, hear. - Okay? Thank you.
祝您愉快
Enjoy.
第二天我去上班
The next day, I got to work,
我都不知道他是怎么知道我在哪里工作的
and I didn't even know how he found out where I worked,
但就是发生了
but there it was.
他在和我调情
He was flirting with me.
已经二十五年没有人和我调过情了
Nobody had flirted with me in 25 years,
让我的心小鹿乱撞
and I had butterflies.
一个小鹿乱撞的成熟女性
Grown-ass woman with butterflies.
真是一个美丽的悲剧
It was beautifully tragic.
在了解一切之前  我喜不自禁
Before I knew it, I was smiling and giddy.
我就像个女学生
I felt like a schoolgirl.
我在想  "为什么  这个人是谁"
I wondered, "Why? Who was this man?
"他为什么要和我调情"
Why was he flirting with me?"
你的埃塞俄比亚女性朋友
邀你共进晚餐
电话434-555-0128
有一个声音在我脑海里高呼
That voice in my head was screaming,
"他想得到什么  他想得到什么"
"What does he want? What does he want?"
但我已经被他迷住了
But I was intrigued.
所以我打给萨拉问我该不该和他约会
So I called Sarah to see if I should go out with him.
你绝对不会相信你的摄影师做了什么
You will not believe what your photographer did.
需要我开车送你去吗
Do you need me to drive you?
-因为你要去  打给他  -什么
- 'Cause you are going. Call him. - What?
打给他
Call him.
好的  好的  我会打的
Okay, okay. I will.
你这个疯狂的催命鬼
You are crazy and pushy.
我等了一天才给他电话
I did wait a day to call him.
我不能表现得很饥渴
I couldn't seem desperate.
打给你
Call you?
我可不这么想  伙计
Yeah, I don't think so, buddy.
但我的好奇心占了上风
But curiosity got the best of me.
第二天去上班时  我对自己说
When I got to work the next day, I said,
"你在搞什么"
"What the hell?"
-喂  -你好
- Hi. - Hi.
你好吗
How are you?
别好像你知道我是谁似的
Oh, don't act like you know who this is.
你是葛蕾丝吧
It's Grace, right?
-是的  -你收到我的照片了吗
- Yeah. - You got my photo?
-是的  收到了  谢谢  -不
- Yes, I did. Thank you. - No.
我可不接受你在电话里感谢
I'm not accepting your thank-you over the phone.
好  好吧
Oh. O-Okay.
-我只接受在晚餐时说的  -好吧
- Only over dinner. - Mm. Okay.
我知道一个完美  小巧
I know this perfect, little, quaint,
复古的小餐馆
hole-in-the-wall diner.
我觉得不错
Well, I-I'm fine with that.
谢谢
Thank you.
跟我说实话
So, tell me something,
你是怎么找到我的
how did you find me?
你在我的来宾名册上签了名
You signed my guestbook.
你也说实话  为什么过了那么久才打给我
Tell me something. Why'd it take you so long to call me?
我在那里遇到了位美丽的女士
I mean, there I was, I met this beautiful woman
我想更多地了解她
that I wanted to know a lot more about,
但她只让我傻站在那里  所以
and she just kinda left me standing there, so...
我知道你身边有很多年轻漂亮的女人
I know you've had many young, beautiful women.
我是说
I mean, um...
我只是想知道
I was just wondering.
为什么是我
Why me?
首先  确实
First of all, yes.
我得到的比我给予的要多
I have had more than my share.
但随着年龄的增长
But as you get older,
那些东西已经不再吸引我
that kind of thing no longer interests you,
而你说的话却让我很感兴趣
and you said something kind of interesting to me.
你说"为什么是我"
You said, "Why me?"
因为人们  我们  总是喜欢这样对自己
As people, we-- we tend to do that to ourselves.
总是问自己"为什么是我  为什么是我"
It's always like, "Why me? Why me? Why me?"
难道不应该问"为什么不是你"
Shouldn't the question be, "Why not you?"
离过婚你就会这样了
Divorce will do that to you.
让你
Make you...
质疑自己是谁
question who you are.
那么  为什么离婚呢
So, why get divorced?
两人的心渐行渐远
People grow apart.
你为什么不结婚
Why aren't you married?
这个问题
That question, yeah.
现在我觉得是因为我从小居无定所
Now, I-I guess it's just 'cause I grew up everywhere,
我总是搬家  典型的军人家庭的孩子
and I was always kind of a gypsy. Military kid.
我去过  纽约  波士顿
Uh, name it, New York, Boston,
亚特兰大  华盛顿  西雅图
Atlanta, DC, Seattle,
韩国  马德里  日本  西非  诸如此类
Korea, Madrid, Japan, West Africa, in that order.
随便说一种文化  我都见过  经历过
Name a culture, I saw it. I experienced it.
但作为一个年轻人
But that was also hard to, you know,
很难定居下来
put down roots as a young man.
我从没想过要结婚
I never wanted to be married.
老实说  我也不想承担这份责任
If I'm honest, I really didn't want the responsibility,
而很多女人都沉迷于此
and a lot of women are into that.
你肯定会惊讶
You'd be surprised, you know.
是  我懂
Yeah, I know.
但对一个孩子来说
Yeah. But that had to be hard as a kid,
居无定所肯定不好过
I mean, living everywhere.
确实  但对一个男人来说却很有趣
It was. But it was fun as a man.
不  不是  我不是说
No, not... I don't...
不是所有事情都跟那个相关
'Cause not everything's about that.
你想歪了
Your mind's in the gutter.
好吗  是的
Okay? Yeah.
没有什么比
I mean, seeing the world...
通过相机镜头来看这个世界
...through the eyes of a 35-millimeter, there's...
更棒的事了
nothing like that.
-这听起来很棒  -是的  我见过很多人
- That sounds like fun. - It was. Met a lot of people.
但我从未遇见过陌生人
But I never met a stranger.
比如  我们
I mean, take us, for example.
-什么  -你和我在一块不舒服吗
- What? - Well, don't you feel comfortable with me?
说实话
Honestly?
老实说  我才刚认识你
Well, honestly, I just met you.
如果我们彼此坦诚  就要一直这样
And if we're being honest, let's keep being honest.
你老这样  你老是
You keep doing this one thing. You keep doing this one--
你有一种模式  你喜欢评头论足
You have a pattern. You judge.
你否认不了  因为我现在正看你这样做
You can't say you don't, because I'm watching you do it.
-好吧  -你喜欢评头论足
- Okay. - You judge.
这只是...
You know, it's just...
这很难接受
It's kinda hard...
当你走进房间  却发现你的丈夫
you know, when you walk in the room, and you...
正在和他的秘书偷情
find your husband having sex with his secretary,
现在她还成了他的妻子
who is now his wife.
对此  我很抱歉
I'm sorry to hear that.
谢谢你
Thank you.
要来点酒吗
Wine?
要
Yes.
我很快就信任了他
I did start to trust him very quickly.
我甚至不明白是为什么
I don't even know why.
他很贴心  而且知道该说什么
He was so kind, and... and he knew what to say.
他很绅士
He was gentle.
我甚至不知道一个男人
I didn't even know that a man could be
可以那样完美  让人感觉那样好
that perfect, feel that perfect.
我不想结束我们的第一次约会
I didn't want our first date to end.
他也不想
And neither did he.
谢谢  凯特琳
Thank you, Kaitlyn.
你前夫有一家抵押贷款公司  是吗
So your ex, he, uh... he owns a mortgage company?
你为什么还提这事
Oh... Why are you still on that?
好吧
Okay.
如果一个男人问起你的前夫
Hint, if a... if a man is asking about your ex,
是因为他想看看自己够不够格
it's because he's trying to see how he measures up.
我能肯定
And from what I can ascertain,
不像我  他很有钱  你也是
unlike me, he's rich, and so are you.
他确实有一家抵押贷款公司
Well, he owns a mortgage company.
但没我的份  我没钱
Mm. Not me. And I'm not rich.
我离婚了  什么都没有了
I left the marriage and everything in it.
你没争财产吗
You didn't fight for the money?
对  完全没有  我什么都不想要
Yeah. Not a thing, you know. No, I didn't want anything.
我只想离婚  我受够欺骗了
I just wanted out. I was... tired of the lies.
我明白
I get that.
我不知道这是为什么
I don't know why that is,
为什么男人很难做到诚实
why men have so much trouble just being honest.
所以你总是说真话吗
And so you always tell the truth?
当然  这有时甚至会给我惹麻烦
Absolutely, 100%. It-- It gets me in trouble sometimes,
因为我总是想什么就说什么
because I have this thing where I just always say what's on my mind.
好吧
Okay.
天啊  已经凌晨两点了
Oh, my God. It is 2:00 a.M.
我明早七点得上班
I have to be at work at, uh, 7:00.
那就这样吧
Quit.
我还能再见你吗
Am I gonna see you again?
你还想再见我吗
Do you wanna see me again?
我不想你现在就离开
I don't want you to leave now.
晚安
Good night.
我甚至不记得我有多久
I didn't even realize how long it had been
没被感动过了
since I had been touched,
多久没有男人向我示好
since I had a man reach for my hand.
我感觉沉寂多年的心又萌动了
I felt something in me that I hadn't felt in years.
我试着去分辨这种感受和情感
I tried to identify the feeling, the emotions,
但我无法集中注意力
but I couldn't bring it into focus
因为它在恐惧中变得温暖起来
because it was warmed over in fear.
我很害怕
I was so terrified.
我头脑中响起了警报
The alarms going off in my head,
我告诉自己  我太老了  没法再谈恋爱
telling myself that I was too old for this shit.
在我脑中我听到他说  他想让我喜欢他
In my head, I'm hearing that he's leading me on,
他是认真的
that he wanted something.
我脑海里一直重复着他说的话
So I kept repeating to myself what he said.
"为什么不是你呢"
"Why not you?"
为什么不是我
Why not me?
我从离婚那天起就一直在祈祷
Maybe God had answered a seven-year-old prayer
也许这是上帝对一个祈祷七年之人的回应
that I had prayed since my divorce.
或许就是他
Maybe this was him.
不知为什么  他甚至比我还了解我自己
Somehow, he knew me almost better than I did myself.
我的脑海里  心里想的都是他
Ooh, he was in my head and well on his way to my heart,
我认识这个男人还不到两天
and I hadn't even known this man for two days.
我知道我很傻
I know I'm a fool.
-你不傻  -那这叫什么
- You're not a fool. - Then what would you call it?
人性
Human.
我不想再谈这个了
I don't wanna talk about this no more.
不行  葛蕾丝  请继续
No. Grace, please.
接着说
Go on.
告诉我
So, tell me.
他是个优雅的绅士
He was a perfect gentleman.
你的梦想是什么
What do you dream about?
梦想常伴随着心痛  所以我没有
Dreams come with heartaches, so no.
不  不  不是
No, no, no, no.
我知道你内心深处还是有梦想的
I know, somewhere in that big heart of yours, you still dream.
说吧
Come on.
我的梦想是做一名好母亲
Well, my dream was to be a great mother.
而且我成功做到了
And I managed to do that.
我有个好儿子
Ah, I got a great kid.
他还得再念两年研究生
Got about two more years in graduate school.
那是我一生中最骄傲的时刻
One of the proudest moments of my life.
好吧
Okay.
一说起你儿子你就很开心
You beam about him when you talk.
哦  那可是我的心头肉
Oh, that's my heart. Ah.
我只是不喜欢她娶的那个贱人
I just don't like the tramp he's married to.
等等  告诉我你真实的感受
Whoa. T-tell me how you really feel.
对不起  上帝  我刚说脏话了
I know. I'm sorry, God. I don't call women names.
你刚刚就说了
You just did.
是啊
Yeah.
只是...
It's just, he...
他应该娶个更好的人
He deserves better.
但我得尊重他的决定
But I gotta let him be an adult, you know?
确实
That you do.
孩子就是孩子  你必须让他们犯错
Boys will be boys. You have to let them make their mistakes.
听起来好像有人犯过一些错
Spoken like someone who's made a few.
何止一些  犯过很多错
More than a few. A lot.
但像你的儿子一样  我也很爱我的母亲
But, like your son, I adored my mother.
你怎么知道他爱我
How do you know he adores me?
他怎么会不爱你
How could he not?
自从她来了  我们就不怎么聊天了
Well, we don't talk as much... since she came around.
这真遗憾
That's a shame.
我以前经常和我母亲聊天
I used to talk to my mother...
每天都聊  有时一天聊三次
every day, three times a day sometimes.
-这太幸福了  -是啊
-Oh, wow, that's beautiful. - Yeah.
我已经连续几个晚上送你回家了
You know, I've been walking you home several nights in a row now.
-对  -这  这很好
- Yeah. - Yeah, it's been-- it's been nice.
但我从来没进过你家
But I've never seen the inside of the house.
我有点好奇是为什么
I'm just kind of wondering why that is.
是因为你家里有个男人吗
Is it because you got a man in there?
这个房子归是你前夫买的吗
Did your ex-husband buy the house?
他正拿了把辛普森那样的刀躲在树丛里吗
Is he hiding in the bushes with an OJ knife?
指美国橄榄球明星辛普森杀妻案
-等等  -他有辆白色野马牌汽车吗
- Oh, wait. - Does he own a white Bronco?
-别说了  -那是怎么回事
- Stop. - What's happening?
不要说了  你知道我现在单身
Just stop. Now, you know I don't have nobody,
房子里没人
and ain't nobody in that house.
而且房子是我买的  谢谢
And I bought my own house, thank you.
对不起
Excuse me.
你知道这栋房子建于十八世纪吗
You know this house was built in the 1800s?
而且是我自己重新装修的  谢谢
And I refurbished it all by myself, thank you.
里面我费尽了心力装修
A lot of blood, sweat, and tears in there.
但我爱这栋房子
But I love it.
这是我买的第一栋房
Very first house I ever bought.
它很漂亮
It's beautiful.
谢谢
Thank you.
我想进去看看
I would love to see the inside.
你一直以来非常绅士  香农
You've been a perfect gentleman, Shannon.
但是...
Mmm, but...
还是不行吗
That's still a no?
目前还不行
For now.
那行
Okay.
明天见
Tomorrow, then.
-行  -还是老时间吗
- Okay. - Same time?
对
Mm-hmm.
-换个地方  好吗  -好
- Different place? - Mm-hmm.
想吃法国菜吗
French, maybe?
-行啊  -你喜欢法国吗
- Okay. - You like French?
是的
Oui, oui.
幸会
Enchanté.
晚安
Good night.
再见
Au revoir.
在我二十几岁时  我会每晚外出
Now, when I was in my 20s, I could do that, out every night,
但到这个年纪不会了
but not so at this time in my life.
虽然工作很累  但没有关系
I was so damn tired at work, but it didn't matter.
我觉得自己又活了过来  我自由了
I felt alive again. I felt free.
我夜夜笙歌
I mean, I was burning the midnight oil
疲惫不堪
and the candle at both ends.
我会在桌旁睡着
I was falling asleep at my desk,
有时和老板一起开会时也会睡着
some days, in meetings with my boss.
我太疯狂了
I was so out of my head,
但我不在乎
but I didn't care.
在那家银行呆了这么多年  我不在乎
All those years at that bank, and I didn't even care.
香农
新信息
我喜欢想起我们在一起的每一刻
I was loving every moment of being thought about
喜欢接到他的电话和短信
and called and texted.
我幸福得像在天堂
I was just in heaven.
♪ 依靠我主耶稣 ♪
♪ Oh! Ride on Jesus ♪
三个月快得就像三天
Three months came and went like three days,
我让他慢慢来
and... and I had held him off,
我知道那个时刻会来临  他在努力
but I knew the time was comin', and, oh, he was trying.
这个男人和我一起去教堂
I mean, the man was going to church with me,
他甚至根本就不信教
and he wasn't even the type at all.
他不喜欢教堂活动
He was not into the church scene.
尽管他不信教  但这仍然很神奇
Despite him not being into the church, it was still magical.
我们有很多共同点
We had so much in common.
我说一句  他就能接下一句
I could start a sentence, and he would finish it.
这太不真实了
It was just unreal.
他就是我的灵魂伴侣
He was really my soulmate.
我找到了我一直寻找的人  这感觉很棒
I had found what I was looking for, and it felt so good.
越来越难坚持住  不让他靠近
It was becoming harder and harder to hold out and keep him at bay.
我在沉沦  弥足深陷
I was falling, and falling hard.
我们会打电话聊一整夜
We'd talk on the phone until the sun came up.
有几次甚至聊睡着了
We even fell asleep on the phone a few times.
我都快不认识我自己了
I didn't even recognize this new person that I had become,
当我试着让自己慢下来时
and when I would tell myself to slow down, slow down,
萨拉就在我身旁
Sarah was right there.
-都怪你  -不 不是
- It's your fault. - No, no, no, no, no.
我从没见你这么高兴过
Oh, I have never seen you this happy.
是的  我很高兴
Oh, girl, I am. I am.
那时  我非常快乐
And I was. I was so happy.
-我好怕  -你相信我吗
- I'm scared. - Do you trust me?
我愿意为他做任何事
I was just about willing to do anything for him.
-你相信我吗  -相信
- Do you trust me? - Yes.
-是什么  亲爱的  -转过来
- Yeah. What is this, baby? What is it? - Turn around.
等一下  不
Ooh, wait, wait, no no, no.
我感觉到有很高的草丛什么的
No, I feel, like, high grass or something.
我可不想被蛇咬  香农
I don't wanna be bit by no snake, Shannon.
好的  听着
Okay, okay, okay, listen.
-我们之前说过的  -好的
- We talked about this. - Yes.
-是的  -你太喜欢评头论足
- Yeah. - You're judging too much.
-好的  好的  -去感受  好吗
- Okay, okay, okay. - Just feel, okay? Just feel.
行  好吧
All right, okay.
这是什么  亲爱的  这是什么
What is this, baby? What is this?
-我眼睛闭上了  -转一圈  转一圈
- My eyes closed... - Spin around, spin around.
-我要闭上眼睛吗  -对
- My eyes closed? - Yes.
-闭上眼睛  转圈  -好吧  好的
- Eyes closed, spin around. - Okay, okay, okay.
好了  睁开眼睛  睁开眼睛
Okay, open, open.
香农  这真漂亮
Oh, Shannon, that's beautiful.
亲爱的  这太美了
Oh, baby, those are beautiful.
天啊
Oh, my God.
快看它们  快看
Look at 'em, look at 'em!
我想找个罐子  你可以把它们抓了装进去
I need a jar. And you can catch 'em and put 'em inside...
你在干什么
What are you doin'?
-葛蕾丝·沃特斯  -你在干什么
- Grace Waters... - What are you doin'?
你愿意嫁给我吗
...will you marry me?
-愿意  -你同意了吗
- Yes. - Is that a yes?
快点  把戒指给我
So, come on, give it to me.
我想都没想就答应了
I said yes before I knew it.
不知为何  我对他无法抗拒
I couldn't resist him for some reason.
他活力四射
He was electric...
总是让我感觉很好
...and so good at making me feel good.
这太不可思议了
It was incredible.
你为什么要拍照片
Why are you takin' pictures?
-往这边挪一点  -我度了大半生
- Move this way... - Most of my entire life lived,
终于遇到他
and here I was.
维多利亚的秘密
Victoria's Secret.
我以为我已经不会再爱了
I thought love was over for me.
我真的这样以为
I really did.
那是我一生中最快乐的时光
Those were the happiest days of my life.
直到
Until...
拜托  告诉我还发生了什么
Please, tell me what else happened.
你认识丹妮尔·米切尔吧
You know Danielle Mitchell.
她死在了这里
She died here.
她曾是你的客户
She was your client.
我知道关于你的一些事  茉莉
Now, I know a little something about you, Jasmine.
你从未辩护过
You've never tried a case.
当他们看到你进来时  都说
And word around here, when they saw you come in...
他们派了个公设辩护人办公室里
was that they had sent me the worst of the worst
最烂的人给我
of the public defender's office.
你赢不了
You don't win.
你只会认罪
You plead.
你就会干这个
That's what you do,
对我来说  也没问题
which was, uh, fine with me.
现在  把笔给我
Now give me the damn pen.
-什么  她这么说的  -对  但她没错
- What, she said all that? - Yeah, but she's right.
我在做什么  我拿到了签字的认罪协议
I mean, what am I doing? I have the signed plea agreement.
我要把它送到地方检察官办公室去
I'm just gonna take it to the DA's office, you know?
我只想结束这一切
I just want to be done with all this.
我只想搬到布鲁克海文
I just want to move to Brookhaven,
生一堆孩子  靠你养家糊口
have a bunch of babies, and have you support the family.
-好的  没问题  -说真的
- Yeah, okay. - Come on.
不  你只可能这样两周
No, that'll last maybe two weeks.
-一周  -对  可能是一周
- One. One. Yeah, probably. Probably one.
我知道这案子还有很多隐情  亲爱的
I just know there's so much more to this story, baby.
我知道有隐情
I just know there is.
-肯定有  -好的
- There is. - Okay. Well...
她已经告诉了你那么多
She told you that much,
不妨让她再告诉你故事的其余部分
just get her to tell you the rest of the story.
不  我不管了
No. I'm done.
我不管了
I'm done.
不  你还得管
No, you're not.
认罪协议办完了吗
Is the plea deal done?
在这一点上
At this point...
如果你想在这里度过余生
if you wanna be in here for the rest of your life,
那就这样吧
so be it.
我手上有你签署的协议
I have your signed agreement.
现在只是等着把它交给地方检察官
I'm just waiting to take it to the DA.
你说的对  我没有赢过任何官司
And you're right about me not winning any cases,
或者根本就没有努力尝试过
or not even trying one for that matter, but...
但我经手的大多是轻罪案
most of my cases were simple misdemeanors
少数几个重罪案我是让其认罪了
or a few felonies that I pled out.
但  葛蕾丝  我从没遇到过像你这样的人
But, Grace, I've never met anyone like you.
我从没遇到过一个
I never met anyone
让我从内心深处感觉到
that I felt, in my heart,
她是无辜的人
was innocent,
即使你告诉我你有罪
even though you're telling me you're guilty.
你知道吗  葛蕾丝  我不知道该怎么帮你
You know, Grace, I don't know how I can help you.
但如果你告诉我发生了什么
But if you tell me what happened...
我保证我会试着帮你的
I promise you I will try.
葛蕾丝  请告诉我还发生了什么事
Grace, please tell me what else happened.
你上次讲到他向你求婚了
You stopped at him asking you to marry him.
我们结婚了
We got married.
那就像一阵旋风
And it was a whirlwind.
是我一生中最快乐的时光
It was the happiest time of my life.
我恋爱了
I was in love.
他就是我理想中的那个男人
He was everything I imagined and wanted in a man.
他说话的方式  抚摸我的方式
The way he spoke, the way he touched me,
和我做爱的方式
and the way he made love to me.
当他抱着我时  我感到非常安全
When he held me, I felt so safe.
我心想  "这怎么可能
I thought, "How is this possible?
每个人都应该如此快乐才对"
Everyone should be this happy."
小女孩
Baby girl.
他很棒
He was wonderful.
我的梦中情人
The man of my dreams.
-来吧  -你做了什么
- Come on. - What have you done?
你知道我做了什么
Ah, you know what I've done.
等等  让我坐起来
Wait, wait, wait, let me sit up.
他曾对我那么好
He was so nice to me.
那么体贴
So sweet.
-不客气  -谢谢你
- You're welcome. - Thank you.
那么和善
So kind.
我枯燥机械的生活
My life went from black-and-white and routine...
变得无比幸福
...to happy and over-the-top.
你好
Hey.
等等  亲爱的
Hold on, hon.
我听说你喜欢红色
I heard you like red.
-是的  而且我喜欢玫瑰  -这是送你的
- Yes, I do, and I love roses. - Those are for you.
这个  是给我的
And... this is for me.
不是吧
Oh, no.
-是的  -不要
- Oh, yes. - No.
是的
Oh, yes.
但这就像看魔术表演一样
But like watching a magic show,
我是如此盲目地深陷爱河
I was so in love and so blinded
眼里只有他想让我看到的东西
by what he was showing me in his hands
我从没想过他背后藏着什么
that I never looked at what he was hiding behind his back.
好了  好了  不要拍了
Okay, okay. Stop.
这些花很漂亮
These are beautiful.
你也是
So are you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
但因为那些快乐时光
But for all those happy days,
我坠入了无边的地狱
I was in for twice as much hell.
所有的一切迅速崩塌  和开始时一样快
And it all started to fall apart as quickly as it began.
不
No.
还没有
Not yet.
你喜欢那些萤火虫吗
Did you enjoy the fireflies?
-你在和谁通话  -我也等不及想见你
- Who are you talking to? - No, I can't wait to see you, too.
好  我明天再打给你
Yeah, I'll call you tomorrow.
再见
Bye.
你在和谁打电话
Who were you talking to?
葛蕾丝
Grace.
怎么了
Yeah?
有两件事我很讨厌
There's two things I don't like.
说吧
Okay.
一个是被查岗
One is being checked up on...
另一个是被怀疑
and the other's being questioned.
好吧
Okay.
我只是  想你了
I just... I just missed you.
我也很想你
I miss you, too.
他为什么非要到楼下打电话
Why did he have to go downstairs to have the conversation?
然后他变得处处提防
And then he got so defensive.
男人有时候就这样  可能没什么
That's just men sometimes. It's probably nothing.
或者  可能他有外遇了
Or it could be another woman.
你知道吗  萨拉
You know what, Sarah?
这一切发生得太快了
This all happened so fast.
好了  葛蕾丝  别小题大做
Okay, Grace, don't go making a mountain out of a molehill.
好吗  可能真没什么
Okay? It's probably nothing.
沃特斯女士
Miss Waters?
等等  怎么了
Hold on. Yes?
克莱德先生在会议室
Mr. Clyde would like to see you
他想马上见您
in the conference room right away, please.
好的  谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
萨拉  我得挂了
Hey, Sarah, I gotta go.
为什么要挂  亲爱的
Why you gotta go, baby?
-我老板想见我  -知道了
- My boss wants to see me. - Oh.
好吧  待会儿再跟你说
Okay, talk to you later.
我还觉得奇怪
I thought it was strange
为什么我老板和公司的管理层
that my boss and all the corporate officers
想在中午的时候见我
wanted to see me in the middle of the day.
我对他将宣布的重大消息一无所知
I had no idea of the bombshell he would drop.
克莱德先生  您想见我吗
Mr. Clyde, you wanted to see me?
我们对你的部门做了内部审计
We just completed an internal audit of your department.
你的账上少了37.9万美元
$379,000 is missing from your accounts.
一定是哪里搞错了
Well, there has to be some mistake.
是用你的公司账号和密码登录的
It was signed for with your company ID, your password,
你电脑的地址  你的笔记本电脑
your computer's IP, your laptop,
你的名字  你的密码
your name, your codes.
你怎么回事  葛蕾丝
What is wrong with you, Grace?
你以为我们会注意不到
You thought that we wouldn't notice
那笔钱被划走了吗
that kind of money being moved?
不  克莱德先生  我  我从没
No, Mr. Clyde, I-I never
你被解雇了
You're fired!
You're fired.
我找不到话来为自己辩解
I couldn't find words to defend myself.
把那笔钱还回来  否则你就去坐牢
I want that money, or you're going to jail.
在我叫保安赶你出去之前  你自己走吧
Now please leave before I have security escort you out.
我太震惊了  他竟然那样对待我
I was just so shocked that he would treat me like that.
他们了解我的
They knew me!
我真不敢相信
I couldn't believe this.
我为这家公司工作了多年
I had worked for this company for years.
它也帮助我过上了好日子
It had helped me have a good life,
现在他们却因为我没做过的事开除我
and they were throwing me out for something I didn't do.
那是一些我永远不会做的事
Something I would never do.
这太可怕了
It was horrible.
我感到很恶心
I felt sick to my stomach.
但我不知道  这还不是最糟的
But little did I know the worst was yet to come.
-他不接电话吗  -不接
- He's not answering? - No.
他可能和昨晚跟他通话的那个人在一起
He's probably with whoever the hell he was talking to on the phone.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
我们刚结婚
We just got married,
他就可能出轨了  而我却傻坐在这里
and he probably with some other woman, and I'm sitting up here,
想搞明白怎么处理这个烂摊子
trying to figure out what to do about this mess!
葛蕾丝  快过来
Grace, Grace, come on now.
冷静点  告诉我你觉得是怎么回事
Calm down, and tell me how you think this happened.
我不知道  萨拉
I don't know, Sarah.
我不知道
I don't know.
我是说
I mean,
也许有人试图
maybe somebody's trying--
有人偷了我的账号  我不知道
Somebody stole my identity. I don't know.
你好
Hey.
你去哪里了
Where you been?
-我给你打了好几个小时电话  -是吗
- I've been calling you for hours. - Have you?
对
Yeah.
-我在  -和你的新欢在一起吗
-I was, uh... - With your new woman?
你也带她去看了  带我去看过的萤火虫吗
You take her to the fireflies like you did me?
萨拉  你能回避一下吗  拜托
Sarah, would you excuse us for a second, please?
不  我哪里也不去
No, I'm not going anywhere.
我想和我妻子谈谈
I'd like to talk to my wife.
我哪里也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
所以  这就是你想做的
So, this is what you wanna do?
你想在你朋友面前跟我吵架吗
You wanna talk to me like this in front of your friend?
她的朋友
Her friend.
谢谢你还记得这点
And you remember that.
没关系  萨拉
It's all right, Sarah.
你确定吗
You sure?
是的
Yeah.
回去吧
Go on.
好吧
All right.
-有事叫我  -会的
- You call me. - Yeah.
她是谁
So, who is she?
你说的是谁
Who is who?
那个女人
The woman.
你去见她了吗
Did you take her?
因为我听见你给她打电话了
'Cause I heard you on the phone.
那天我是在和护士打电话
I was talking to the nurses.
护士长  她六十岁了
The head nurse, she's 60.
我去给孩子们拍了这些照片
I set up this photo shoot with the kids.
之前也给你拍过
Kind of did it for you.
他们得了癌症  葛蕾丝
They have cancer, Grace.
我以为你会喜欢这些照片
I figured you'd like the shoot because...
因为那是我向你求婚的地方
that's where I proposed to you.
你知道不会发生什么吗
You know what's not gonna happen?
因为我们已经讨论过了
Because we already discussed this.
我不想坐在这里听你指责我
I'm not gonna sit here and be acc...
你猜怎么着  去他妈的
You know what? Fuck this.
等等  亲爱的  对不起
Wait, baby. I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我刚刚经历了人生中最糟的一天
Listen, I just had one of the worst days of my life.
我被炒了
I got fired.
-被炒了  -对
- Fired? - Yeah.
我都不知道发生了什么
I don't know what happened,
有人进了我的账户  他们有我的密码
but somebody got into my accounts, they got my passwords...
我不知道
I don't know.
-我不知道该怎么办  -抱歉  亲爱的
- I don't know what to do. - I'm sorry. I'm sorry, baby.
我给银行打了一整天的电话
I mean, I've been calling the banks all day.
我觉得  我觉得可能是有人
I-I think-- I think somebody maybe...
可能有人盗取了我的身份信息
Maybe somebody stole my identity.
-亲爱的  -我不知道该怎么做
- Baby, - I don't know what to do.
亲爱的  没事的  好吗
Baby, it's okay, it's okay. Okay?
我们会解决这件事的
Look, we're gonna handle it.
-好的  -我陪着你
- OK. - I'm here.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
不  我很抱歉  很抱歉会发生这种事
No, I-I'm sorry. I'm sorry this happened.
我们会搞清楚的  告诉我该给谁打电话
We're gonna make it right. Just tell me who call.
不知道  试着打给
I don't know... start t-trying to call
我的信用账户之类的
my credit accounts or something like that.
我不知道该打给谁
I don't know who all to call.
也许该打给国税局  我不知道
Maybe I'll try to call the IRS. I don't know.
-我们一起想办法  -好的
- We'll figure it out together. - Okay.
别着急  别着急
This is... Just breathe, just breathe.
-过来  别着急  -谢谢
- Come here, breathe. - Thank you.
他真的很
He was so...
很担心
...concerned.
-来吧  给他们打电话  -好吧
- Come on. Let's call 'em. - Okay.
我们得搞定这件事
We gotta get this.
我们几乎一夜没睡  试着搞清发生了什么
We stayed up most of the night trying to figure out what happened.
你想到谁了  想到谁了
Who do you got? Who you got?
还是税务局的  我再试试
Uh, the IRS again. Let me try...
第二天  我起得很早
The next morning, I got up really early
报了警
and called the police.
他们根本帮不上忙  你们有什么办法吗
They were no help at all, so... Is there anything you can do?
我去了银行
...I went to the bank.
抱歉  请问这是你的签名吗
I'm sorry, is this your signature?
和你的印鉴卡一模一样
It matches your signature card.
看上去像是我的签名  但这是什么
Well, it looks like mine, but, uh, what is that?
因为我根本没签过
'Cause I didn't sign it.
我们想知道你什么时候
We need to know when you can
可以还抵押贷款
make the payment on your mortgage.
已经逾期三十天了
It's 30 days behind.
什么抵押贷款
What mortgage?
我的房款四年前就付清了
My house has been paid for for over four years.
没错
Well, it was,
然后你抵押了37.5万美元
and then you took out a $375,000 mortgage
确切的说  是四十二天前
exactly 42 days ago.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
付款已被直接取走
The payments were set up as direct withdrawal,
现在你的帐户透支了
and your account is now overdrawn by...
四千六百美元
$4,600.
等等
Wait a minute.
这不对
This can't be right.
等等
Wait a minute.
这不是我做的
I didn't do this.
就像我跟你的一个出纳员所说的
But as I was trying to tell one of your tellers,
我认为是人盗取了我的身份信息
I think that somebody has stolen my identity.
明白吗  怎么会发生这种事
See, because how is this kind of stuff even possible?
因为我没签过这个  我从没来过这里
'Cause I didn't sign this, and I never came in here.
这不是我的签的
This was not me.
已经公证了
It was notarized.
谁公证的
By whom?
弗林奇公证处
Uh... Flynch Notary.
等等  我可以借用一下吗  抱歉
Hold on, can I just borrow this for a minute? Excuse me.
-弗林奇公证处  -弗林奇公证处
- Flynch Notary. - Flynch Notary.
地址是西卡摩街2989号
the address is 2989 Sycamore Street.
主啊  发发慈悲吧
Lord, have mercy.
然后呢
What is going on?
很抱歉  在调查这件事的过程中
I'm sorry, but while we look into this,
我们还是需要你还款
we're gonna need a payment
这样你的房子才不会被没收拍卖
so your house doesn't go into foreclosure.
明白了
Okay.
然后呢
What is going on?
我去了西卡摩街
I went to Sycamore Street,
那是一座废弃的老房子
and it was an old, abandoned house.
邮件堆积如山
The mail was piling up. It was...
都是寄给一个叫阿·麦卡西的人
All of it was addressed to somebody named A. McKathy.
我很生气  一个陌生人居然这样坑我
I was just upset that some stranger would do this to me.
这太可怕了
It was horrible.
我回到银行
I went back to the bank
调取监控录像  然后
to get video surveillance, and... and, well...
那时我所知道的一切都破灭了
That's when everything I knew shattered.
是你干的
You did it.
什么
What?
你还好吗
You okay?
是你干的
You did it.
干了什么
Did what?
你去了我的银行
You went to my bank,
拿我的房子做了抵押
and you took out a mortgage on my house.
葛蕾丝  我不知道你在说什么
Grace... I don't know what you're talking about.
看看你的手机
Check your cell.
葛蕾丝
Grace...
我需要那笔钱  葛蕾丝
I needed the money, Grace.
哪个男人想向女人要钱
And what kind of man wants to ask his woman for money?
别这样
I mean, come on.
我有些债必须还给别人
I had debts that had to be paid by some people
这些债必须还
that are not to be messed with.
我只是觉得我们是夫妻  已经结婚了
And I just thought because we're partners, we're married,
所以我认为
so I just figured that...
你会给我那些钱
you'd want me to have it.
-你为什么不给  -天啊
- Why don't you - Oh, my God.
-你还偷了我单位的公款  -我没有
- You stole the money from my job, too. - I did not.
-你有  -我会还给你的  我会的
- Yes, you did! -I'll pay you back. I'm gonna--
我的账户
My accounts?
我  我的密码
My-- My-- My passwords?
是你做的吧  香农
You did that, Shannon?
是你干的
You did that.
不
No.
N-no.
我希望你把所有的钱
I want you to give me back...
都还给我
all that money.
我会坐牢的
I can go to jail.
钱在哪里
Where-- Where is it?
你得把钱还给我
I need you to give me back that money.
-不可能  -你说什么
- I can't. - What the hell?
现在是我的钱了
It's mine now.
你他妈的说什么
What the fuck are you talkin' about?
你了解本州的法律吗
Do you know the laws of this state?
因为我了解
Because I do.
作为你的合法丈夫
And as your lawfully wedded husband,
我有权花这笔钱
I have every fucking right to that money!
你得庆幸我有两部手机
You lucky I got two phones.
他还在说  而我什么也听不到了
He was talkin', and I didn't hear anything.
我不敢相信
I couldn't believe this.
我被骗了
I had been conned.
所有的一切都是谎言
All of it was a lie.
我明白  但我的大脑接受不了他所做的事
I knew it, but my brain couldn't process what he had done.
我一无所有
There I was with nothing.
他拿走了我的一切
He had taken every bit of it,
我输得很彻底
and I was so lost.
当初这个甜蜜可人的男人
How could this sweet, loving man
一瞬间变成了冷酷又算计的魔鬼
become this cold, calculating demon in no time?
我受不了这种背叛
I was beyond hurt by the betrayal.
你给我滚出我的房子
I want you out of my house.
滚出这里
I want you out of my house,
立刻马上滚出去
and I want you out of my house, now.
把烟灰缸拿给我
And I want an ashtray.
你个狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
他在嘲笑我
He was laughing at me.
你一直在说"你的房子"
You keep saying "your house."
结婚证证明这是我们的房子
That marriage license says our house.
他拿走我的钱就已经够坏了
It was bad enough that he had taken all my money,
但他还在那里嘲笑我
but here he was laughin'.
-等着瞧  -我等着
- You watch. - I'm watchin'.
烟灰缸
Ashtray.
烟灰缸  婊子
Ashtray, bitch!
他不愿意走
And he wouldn't leave.
我报了警  我告诉了他们所有的事
I called the police. I told them everything.
这座房子不属于他
He does not own this house,
我买下这座房子四年了
I've owned this house for four years.
但是他们说他们无能为力
They told me that there was nothing they could do,
他们说我需要一名律师  因为这是民事案件
and that I needed a lawyer because this was a civil matter.
萨拉认识一位律师  我们去见了他
Sarah recommended a lawyer, and we went to see him.
一万美元
Ten thousand dollars?
律师告诉我他的佣金是一万美元
The attorney told me that his retainer was $10,000,
而且可能要等两年才能上法庭
and it could be as long as two years to get to court.
他已经拿了我这么多  萨拉
He's already taken so much-- Sarah.
我无计可施
My hands were tied.
我不知道该怎么办  我真不甘心
I didn't know what to do. I was just so outdone.
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
别急嘛
Not yet.
香农  你他妈从我的房子里滚出去
Shannon, get your black ass out of my motherfucking house!
快滚
I mean it!
他妈的尊重一下我的隐私
Respect my motherfucking privacy!
狗娘养的  你个狗娘养的
You son of a bitch! You son of a bitch!
我得给这些门上装把锁
Get some goddamn locks on these doors.
你这个混蛋
You black-ass bastard!
狗杂种
You son of a bitch!
什么
What?
你带我来你妈家
So, you brought me to your mom's house?
我妈住得比这里好
My momma live better than that.
-我们进行到哪里  -拜托
- Where were we? - Come on.
别管这些
Don't worry about it.
我悲痛欲绝
Then it washed over me.
心灰意冷
I went numb.
你体会过那种心灰意冷的感觉吗
You ever had that numb feeling?
就像你所经历的都不是真的
Like what's going on with you can't be real?
这不可能是真的
It just can't be.
我不敢相信我这种年纪
I couldn't believe that I was this age
还会让这种事发生在自己身上
and I let this happen to me.
这真棒
That was great.
我们还会见面吗
Will I see you again?
行  只要你妈不再冲进来
Yeah, if your mom don't break in on us again.
她不会的
She won't.
我有蠢到让这种情况发生吗
Was I that stupid that I would let this happen?
那不是我
Not me.
我受过教育
I'm educated
很聪明
and smart.
我真的孤独到
Was I that lonely...
会让这个蠢货
...that I would let this fool
占我的便宜吗
take advantage of me?
我不明白
I didn't understand it.
你应该加入我们
Should've joined us.
你以前这副表情就吓到过我  亲爱的
That look killed me, baby.
现在的表情和那时候一个样
It's kind of like the same one you got now.
香农  请把我的钱还给我
Shannon, please give me my money.
什么
What?
我就快被公司起诉了
I'm looking at being prosecuted by my job.
-葛蕾丝  又来了吗  -把我的钱给我
- Grace, again with that? - Give me my money.
-求求你  -葛蕾丝  葛蕾丝  葛蕾丝
- Please. - Grace, Grace, Grace,
葛蕾丝  葛蕾丝  葛蕾丝  葛蕾丝
Grace, Grace, Grace, Grace.
在我来看
Now, the way I look at it...
那些钱是你欠我的
you owe me that money.
是的  你想想
Yeah. I mean, think about it.
所有你享受到的性爱
All the sex...
以及我给你悲惨生活带来的欢乐
and the joy I brought to your miserable fucking life!
对
Yeah.
你欠我的
You owe me.
我的意思是
I mean... um...
我不是故意要对你大喊大叫
I don't mean to yell.
你是一个好人  葛蕾丝
You're a nice lady, Grace.
你是一个非常好的人
You're a very nice lady.
真的是我见过最好的人  真的
One of the nicest I ever met, really.
这就是为什么我一直很难下手
That's why it's been so hard for me to do this.
是啊
Yeah.
我想我能做的最好的事就是告诉你真相
I guess the nicest thing I can do is tell you the truth.
你看  我是爱你的
You see, I love you.
我真的爱你  我
I really do love you. I...
我只是不能像你爱我那样来爱你
I'm just never gonna love you the same way that you love me.
像你这个年纪的女人  你知道
And women your age, you know...
要怎么说
How's the phrase go?
特别容易上钩
Low-hanging fruit.
单身
Single.
脆弱
Vulnerable.
孤独
Lonely.
特别软弱
Fuckin' weak.
如果你仔细想想
I mean, if you think about it...
这都是你的错
it's your fuckin' fault.
你让这一切太容易
You made this too easy.
但你不想想
But you don't think.
葛蕾丝  我
Grace, I'm hun--
我不敢相信我竟然杀了他
I couldn't believe that I had killed him.
我坐上我的车  然后就一直开
I got in my car, and I just drove...
一直开
and drove.
当我清醒过来  我在极偏僻的地方
Before I knew it, I was in the middle of nowhere.
萨拉
Sarah.
他在我家地下室
He's in my basement.
我杀了他
I killed him.
你告诉萨拉你杀了他
You told Sarah you killed him?
对
Yes.
-你没有把尸体移走  -没有
- And you didn't remove the body? - No.
我把他留在那里了
I left him there.
萨拉去了我家
Sarah went to the house.
然后她打电话告诉我
Then she called me and told me
那里没有尸体
there wasn't a body.
他不见了
He was gone.
等等  你是在说他没死吗
Wait, are you telling me he's not dead?
不  我知道他死了
No, I know he's dead.
但他就是不在那里
But he wasn't there.
时间到
Time's up.
葛蕾丝  尸体在哪里
Grace, where was the body?
他在哪里
Where was he?
我不知道
I don't know.
你没跟我说  她告诉过你她杀了他
You didn't tell me she told you she killed him.
这种事情你不能瞒着我  萨拉
You can't keep this kind of thing from me, Sarah.
我想帮她
I'm trying to help her,
这种信息我必须知道
and this is the kind of information that I need to know.
所以你去了她家
So you went to her house?
对
Yes.
那你到了之后发生了什么
And what happened when you got there?
不管你说什么我都不会用来对她不利
There is nothing you can say that I can use against her.
好吗
Okay?
我担心的不止是她
It's not just her I'm worried about.
那是谁
Who?
如果你知道一些事情  却没告诉警察
If you knew something and you didn't tell the police,
这是犯罪  对吗
that's a crime, right?
如果地方检察官知道了  是的
If the DA knew this, then, yes.
你会被指控
You would be charged.
不是我
Not me.
她的儿子  马尔科姆
Her son, Malcolm.
他在那里
He was there.
马尔科姆吗
Malcolm?
那么他说了什么吗
Well, did he say anything?
你看到什么异常了吗
Did you see anything unusual?
他只是有点激动
He was just a little agitated, and...
太快了  他开车走了
it was quick, you know? He-- He just drove away.
那你进了屋后发生了什么
Well, what happened when you got in the house?
我去了地下室  但那里没有尸体
I went down to the basement, but there was no body there.
到处都是血迹  地下室楼梯上都是血迹
There was just blood everywhere, all over the basement stairs.
你觉得发生了什么
What do you think happened?
我觉得马尔科姆
I think Malcolm...
在我到那里之前带走了尸体
took the body before I got there...
或者
or...
或者葛蕾丝在头脑不清醒的情况下
Or if Grace was in a state of shock,
可能把尸体拖上来
she might have dragged that body up
装进了她的汽车后备箱
and put it in the back of her car,
开车到郊外  然后把尸体扔在了某处
drove out to the country, and dumped it somewhere.
不  没有  她没那么做
Mm-mm. No, no. No, no. She didn't do that.
我相信她
I believe her.
我只是太爱她了
I just love her so much.
很抱歉  萨拉女士
I'm sorry, Miss Sarah.
我只是  我
I just... I...
你已经为她尽力了  萨拉女士
You did all you could for her, Miss Sarah.
-没关系的  -我抱歉  萨拉女士
- It's all right. It's all right. - I'm so sorry, Miss Sarah.
-我会处理好的  -好  好的
- I'll fix it. - Okay, okay.
现在我们知道了她为什么想认罪
Now we know why she wants to plead guilty.
为什么
Why?
为了保护她儿子
To protect her son.
-亲爱的  你要睡觉了吗  -等一会儿
- Baby, you coming to bed? - In a little bit.
亲爱的  你明天上班时
Oh, babe, when you get to work tomorrow,
能查一下香农·德隆吗
can you look up Shannon Delong,
别让别人知道
without anybody noticing?
我真的不应该那么做
Uh, I really shouldn't do that.
求你了
Please?
好吧  我看看我能做什么
Okay. I'll see what I can do.
谢谢
Thank you.
所以  她在试图保护她儿子和萨拉
So you see, she's trying to protect her son and Sarah.
现在我需要你们的帮助
Now I need your help.
茉莉  到我办公室来
Jasmine, my office.
今天晚上七点我家见  你们两个都来
Meet me at my house at 7:00, both of you,
好吗
okay?
好吧
All right.
她真的打算为她辩护了
She's really gonna defend her.
是啊
Yeah,
除非主张认罪协议的罗里先生不让她那么做
not if Mr. Rory Plea-Deal has anything to say about it.
你说的对
You right.
我明白了  多谢
I got it. Thanks.
是地方检察官办公室打来的
That was the DA's office.
你想解释一下为什么
You wanna tell me why
他们还没收到葛蕾丝·沃特斯的认罪协议吗
they don't have the plea from Grace Waters yet?
事情有变  她不想认罪了
There's been a change of events. She doesn't want to plead guilty.
她想庭审此案
She wants to try the case.
她负担不起出庭的费用
She can't afford to go to trial.
我们也负担不起出庭的费用
This office cannot afford to go to trial.
你应该干什么  你应该让她认罪
What are you gonna do? You gonna plead.
已经三周过去了
It's three weeks away.
这就是你打算做的吗
Is that what you're planning on doing?
是的
Yes.
很好
That's great.
你现在突然想当英雄了
Now all of a sudden you want to be this hero
你想出庭辩护吗
and you want to try a case?
你还没准备好  我一直在观察你
You're not ready. I've been watching you.
我给你这个案子是有原因的
I gave you this for a reason,
你擅长做认罪
you plea.
你接下来该这么做
Here's what you're gonna do.
你去监狱
You're gonna go down to that jailhouse,
让她在认罪书上签字
and you're gonna get her to sign that plea,
顺利完成此事
and you're gonna get it done.
没关系  我来做  我来  谢谢
Never mind, I'll do it. I'll do it. Thanks.
葛蕾丝  我时间不多了  现在
Grace, I don't have a lot of time. Now...
我觉得我们有足够多的合理性怀疑
I think we have enough reasonable doubt
去让陪审团注意
to get that into the jury's mind,
这意味着你可能会被判无罪
and that means an acquittal.
地方检察官接受认罪协议了吗
Did the DA take the deal?
不  不  听我说
No, no, no. No, listen to me.
我知道他死的那天
I know Sarah and your son
萨拉和你儿子都去过那个房子
were at the house the day he died.
谁告诉你的
Who told you that?
这是我的事
This is my mess.
是我把他们卷进来的
I dragged them into this,
我不会让我儿子进监狱的
and I will not let my son go to jail.
是你儿子帮你处理的尸体吗
Did your son help you get rid of the body?
不  他没有  别再问我这个问题
No, he did not, and don't you ever ask me that again.
好吧  你听着  我的上司随时可能进来
Okay, look, my boss is gonna walk into that door any minute,
我要你告诉他你改主意了
and I need you to tell him that you have changed your mind,
你不想认罪
and you do not want a plea.
我对地方检察官的唯一要求
The only thing I asked the DA to do
就是把我关在离我儿子近的监狱
was to put me in a prison close to my son,
你想让我毁掉这个协议吗  绝不
and you want me to jeopardize that? No!
-但如果你无罪释放了呢  -你做不到
- But what if you go free? - You can't do that.
对
Yeah,
如果你不让我帮你辩护  我没办法做到
I know I can't if you don't let me fight for you!
求求你  让我帮你辩护吧
Please, let me fight for you!
我能做到
I can do it.
茉莉  我就知道你在这里
Jasmine, I had a feeling you'd be here.
你好
Hi.
我是罗里·加罗  茉莉的上司
My name is Rory Garraux. I'm Jasmine's boss.
我认为她一直在向你传递错误的信息
And I think that she's been giving you some misleading information.
我希望你明白
I'd like you to understand something.
我们反复看过你的案子
My office has looked at your case up and down,
我们认为认罪协议是个好主意
and we think a plea is a good idea.
那样的话  你可以离你儿子近一点
That way, you can be near your son.
我知道那对你来说很重要  对吧
I know that's important to you, yes?
所以我今天来的目的是想知道
So my purpose here today is to find out
你是否依然想认罪
if it's still your intention to plead guilty.
沃特斯女士  你想认罪吗
Miss Waters, is it your intention to plead guilty?
我想要庭审
I wanna go to court.
会见室
我知道是你说服她这么做的
I know you talked her into this.
在监狱内
从事任何
性活动
都是重罪
这个案子你要是输了
When you lose this case,
我向你保证
I promise you,
你会被解雇  你的职业生涯到此为止
you're fired, and your career's over.
希望我不会因此丢掉我的工作
Hope I don't lose my job,
但是我查过了  他没有前科
but I ran him, and he's clean.
该死  他是个行骗高手
Damn it. He's a con artist.
他可能有好几个化名
He probably has several different aliases.
好吧  你知道他其他的名字吗
Well, okay. Uh, do you know any of them,
或者你有指纹之类的吗
or do you have fingerprints or something?
我的天啊
Oh, my God. Um...
试试这个  虽然是老照片了
Try this. It's a long shot,
但看看有没有什么发现
but see what happens.
好把  亲爱的  我在开玩笑
Okay. Babe, I was kidding,
很好  又多了一件让我被开除的事
but great. Another thing to get me fired.
谢谢  亲爱的  好的
Thanks, babe. Okay.
我要传唤萨拉出庭作证
Um... I'm gonna call Sarah to the stand.
我不知道  可能会很棘手
I don't know, that could be tricky.
地方检察官不知道她打过电话给她
The DA doesn't know that she called her.
但如果他够厉害
But if he's good,
他可能会从她嘴里套出话来
he could potentially get it out of her.
不  不会  她很坚强
No, no, no. No. She's strong.
-我不知道  茉莉  -她很坚强
- I don't know, Jasmine. - She's strong.
这样真的很冒险
That's, uh, really risky.
我需要建立她是个好人的人设
I need to establish that she's a good person,
还有比她最好的朋友更好的人选吗
and what better person to do that than her best friend?
-对吗  -对的
- Right? - Yeah.
对  确实是
Yeah, that's true.
我不知道  我什么都不知道了
I-I don't know. I don't know anymore.
除了满地血迹和消失的尸体我们还有什么
Well, what else do we have besides blood pooling and no body? Huh?
好吧  我们只需要合理性怀疑
Okay. All we need is reasonable doubt.
好吧  我们再来一遍
Okay, let's just start again.
我们都看了三遍了  这里什么都没有
This is the third time we've started. Look, there's nothing here.
好吗  没有确凿证据
Okay? There's no smoking gun.
我们需要找到足够的间接证据
Well, we need to find enough circumstantial evidence
来证明这一点
to become one.
怎么了
What?
没什么  那股激情
Nothing. The fire.
我们喜欢
We love it.
-我再看一遍  -我来看这个  茉莉
- I'll start again. - I'm gonna take this file, Jasmine.
你负责电话记录
You get the phone records.
开庭陈词
Opening statements.
陪审团的女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury.
今天  我们会毫无疑问地证明
Today, we are gonna prove, without a reasonable doubt,
这个女人
that this woman...
葛蕾丝·安妮·沃特斯
Grace Anne Waters,
冷血地谋杀了香农·德肖恩·德隆
murdered Shannon DeShawn Delong in cold blood.
她怎么做的呢
How'd she do it?
她用一根棒球棍
Well, she took a baseball bat,
就像这根
like this one...
生生把他打死了
and she beat him to death.
不仅如此  证据将表明她是怎么做的
Not only that, the evidence is gonna show how she did it.
她的动机能够解释  她为什么要这么做
The motive will show why she did it.
但告诉人们
And it's up to you
违背法律的后果是什么  这取决于你们
to show what happens to people who break the law.
像葛蕾丝·安妮·沃特斯这样的冷血杀手
People like Grace Anne Waters who are cold-blooded killers.
像她这样  对人的生命
People with no regard...
毫无敬意的人
for human life.
这次  你们有机会
You have a chance, at this time,
把葛蕾丝·安妮·沃特斯  一个杀人犯
to take Grace Anne Waters, a murderer...
永远地从社会中驱逐出去
off the streets forever.
布莱恩特女士
Mrs. Bryant?
Mrs. Bryant.
你的开庭陈词
Opening statements?
你们已经听过了控方陈述
You've heard the prosecution assert
说有证据证明她是有罪的
that there is evidence to prove that she is guilty.
我想让你们知道的是
Well, we want you to know...
同样的这些证据
that that same evidence will prove
将证明她是无罪的
that she is not guilty.
葛蕾丝·沃特斯不是一名冷血的杀手
Grace Waters is not a cold-blooded killer.
她是一个奶奶
She's a grandmother.
她给流浪汉食物
She feeds the homeless.
她在主日学校教书
She teaches Sunday school.
她烤饼干
She bakes cookies.
看看她吧
Just look at her.
看看她
Look at her.
对于她而言  这就像一场噩梦
This is a nightmare for her,
对于任何一个以谋杀罪受审的
and as it can be for anyone who is on trial for murder
无辜的人来说都是
and is innocent.
葛蕾丝爱他的丈夫
Grace loved her husband,
她没有导致她丈夫的失踪
and she did not cause his disappearance.
我之所以说  "失踪"
And the reason I say "disappearance"
是因为  从证据来看  一直以来
is because the evidence will show that there is, not now,
直至现在  都没有证据表明有谋杀发生
nor has there ever been, any evidence that a murder happened.
没有发现尸体
No body found.
这是因为她没有杀他
That's because she did not murder him.
超越合理怀疑
Beyond reasonable doubt.
你们得忽略之前的结论
That's the conclusion you need to get past
才能做出裁决
in order to reach a verdict.
这个案子还有很多疑点
There are a lot of doubts here.
它们都不合理
And they're all beyond reasonable.
你们会发现的
You'll see. You'll see.
说得真好
Wow, that was good.
不用怀疑她
Mm. Don't doubt her.
当她不再怀疑自己的时候会容易得多
It'll be a lot easier when she stops doubting herself.
传唤你的第一位证人
Call your first witness.
指控方传唤马歇尔·托马斯警探
Prosecution calls Detective Marshall Thomas.
以作伪证应负惩罚为后果
Do you solemnly affirm that you will tell the truth,
你庄严承诺  尽其所知
the whole truth and nothing but the truth
所述之言纯属实言并且无任何隐瞒
under the pains and penalties of perjury?
-我宣誓  -托马斯警探
- I do. - Detective Thomas...
你是被叫到布鲁本巷1828号的警察吗
were you the officer that was called to 1828 Bruben Lane?
是的
Yes.
你们找到尸体了吗
Did you find a body?
我们没有
No, we didn't.
所以你们假设这是死者的血液
So you assumed that this was blood loss.
不是假设  我们检测过DNA
No assumption, we have DNA testing.
DNA检测能确定血是什么时候留下的吗
Well, can your DNA test determine when that blood was left there?
不能  血迹已经被清理干净
No, the stains were cleaned up.
所以现场血迹有可能
So it's a possibility that the blood
在那里存在了很长一段时间
could have been left there over time?
可能吧  但是这不
I suppose, but that's not--
比如不同时间多次累加到等量血迹
Like over several different times to add up to that same amount?
这几乎不可能
That's highly unlikely.
我没问你可能不可能
I didn't ask if it was likely,
我问的是  理论上有没有可能发生
I asked was it reasonably possible that that could happen?
有  任何事都有可能
Yes. Anything's possible.
我没有其他问题了
No further questions.
这种血迹喷溅
The blood spatter.
钝器伤的喷溅在这个位置正常吗
Is that normal in this position for blunt force trauma?
是的
Yes.
我看到这个照片  我看到
See, so when I looked at this, I saw--
反对  法官阁下  这不是问题
Objection, Your Honor. Is there a question here?
反对有效
Sustained.
现场血迹有可能是原始血迹已经存在时
So the trajectory of the blood could have been from
又被其他东西击中  所形成的吗
something hitting it after it was already there?
是的
Yes.
我没有其他问题了
No further questions.
你记得你八月十七日晚上在哪里吗
Do you remember where you were the night of August the 17th?
你吸毒吗
Do you use illegal narcotics?
你跟德隆先生一起工作吗
So you worked with Mr. Delong?
你觉得他是个有责任心的年轻人吗
Did you find him to be a responsible young man?
你跟他上过床吗  女士
Have you slept with him, ma'am?
-反对  -反对有效
- Objection. - Sustained.
当他要求给你拍照片时  他有调情吗
When he asked to take your picture, was he flirty?
你让他这么做了吗
Did you let him?
反对  法官阁下  不能作为证词
Objection, Your Honor, move to strike.
-反对理由  -法官阁下
- On what grounds? - Your Honor
别让我再警告你
Don't make me warn you again.
你在商店里见过他吗
Did you meet him there in the store?
你知道他已经结婚了吗
Did you know he was married?
你见过她和几个男人一起来教堂
How many men have you seen her in church with?
她跟这些男人有感情关系吗
Was she affectionate with these men?
反对  法官阁下
Objection, Your Honor.
反对无效
Overruled.
我们现在怎么样
How we doing?
控方正在推翻我们的证词
Well, the prosecutor is blowing us out the water.
现在  你知道我没给你儿子打电话
Now, you know I did not call your son.
谢谢
Thank you.
但是我可以叫萨拉出庭作证
But Sarah I can call to the stand,
然后  通过问是不是她杀了香农
and, um, I can raise reasonable doubt
我可以提出合理怀疑
by simply asking if she killed Shannon.
-听我说  -不行
-Listen. - No.
你没听我说吗  她是我朋友
Now, you don't listen, do you? That is my friend.
葛蕾丝  我真的觉得我们有机会
Grace, I really feel like we have an in there
-只要我们  -茉莉
- if we can just. - Jasmine.
你敢做  我保证
Do it, and I promise you,
我当场就承认我有罪
I will stand up and scream I did it, that I'm guilty.
好吧
Okay.
知道了
All right.
控方的证人们太有力了
Wow, the prosecution has some unbelievably strong witnesses.
-我知道  -那你准备怎么办呢
- I know. - So what are you gonna do?
我必须叫萨拉出庭作证
I have to call Sarah to the stand.
茉莉  如果你不去盘问她
Jasmine, if you don't go after her
告诉陪审团一些东西
and give the jury something...
你认为我不知道吗
Don't you think I know that?
但你不能只让她当个品德证人
Okay, but you need her to be more than just a character witness.
这个我也知道  我不能突然问她其他问题
I know that, too. And I can't go left on her,
不然葛蕾丝就输了
or Grace'll lose it.
我还不能问她香农和葛蕾丝的关系
And I can't ask her about Shannon and Grace's relationship,
因为指控方会用这个当作新的动机
because that'll give the prosecution another motive.
我知道  唐尼  好吗
I got it, Donnie. Okay?
好
Okay.
我只是想帮忙  好吗
You know I'm just trying to help, right?
-谢谢  -不客气  女士
- Thanks. - Yes, ma'am.
宝贝  睡觉吧
Babe, sleep.
睡不着
I can't.
会没事的
It's gonna be fine.
会的
It will.
我只希望萨拉别搞砸了
I just hope Sarah doesn't blow it.
你  唐尼和特利萨已经帮她准备好了吧
Well, you, Donnie, and Tilsa prepped her, right?
对  但是
Yeah, but...
我只剩她了
she's all I have.
别紧张  我明天会早点下班
Stop stressing. I'm gonna be off early tomorrow.
我会尽快赶过去
I'm gonna get there as soon as I can.
我会看着你把它拿下的  好吗
I'm gonna watch you knock it out, okay?
现在  睡觉吧
Now, go to sleep.
米勒女士
Miss Miller,
你能告诉法庭你和葛蕾丝的关系吗
can you tell the court about your relationship with Grace?
我们是好的朋友
We're best friends.
你们的关系有多好
And how close are you two?
她就像是我的妹妹
She's like the sister I never had.
你们认识多久了  米勒女士
And how long have you known each other, Miss Miller?
六年了
For six years.
在认识她的这段时间里  米勒女士
And in that time of knowing her, Miss Miller,
你见过葛蕾丝很暴力或者很愤怒吗
have you ever seen Grace violent or angry?
没有
Oh, no. Oh, no.
哪怕在该动粗的时候她也不是个暴力的人
She's not a violent person, even when she should be.
你这话什么意思
What do you mean by that?
我见过有人很刻薄地对待葛蕾丝
I have seen people be very mean to Grace,
但是她依然为他们祈祷
and she just prayed for them.
现在  米勒女士  控方想让我们相信
Now, the prosecution wants us to believe, Miss Miller,
葛蕾丝是一个冷血的杀手
that Grace is a cold-blooded murderer.
-反对  -反对有效
- Objection. - Sustained.
最后警告  布莱恩特女士
I'm not gonna warn you again, Mrs. Bryant.
只问问题
Ask a question.
米勒女士
Miss Miller,
葛蕾丝有能力杀人吗
is Grace capable of murdering someone?
葛蕾丝吗  不  不会的
G-Grace? Oh, no. No, no.
她永远不会伤害任何人  她不会
She would never hurt anyone. She wouldn't.
她有能力用球棒打人吗
Is she capable of beating someone with a bat?
绝对没有
Absolutely not.
我没有其他问题了
No further questions.
谢谢  米勒女士
Thank you, Miss Miller.
米勒女士
Miss Miller,
你说过你们是好朋友  对吗
you say the two of you were close friends?
对
Yes.
当她有麻烦时会打电话给你吗
So would she call you when she was in trouble?
不
No.
-她不会吗  -我意思是  是的
- She wouldn't? - I mean, yes.
是的  她会
Yes, she would.
八月十七日晚
Well, did she call you on the...
她给你打过电话吗
the night in question, August 17th?
我知道你想保护你的朋友
I know you want to protect your friend.
反对  法官阁下
Objection, Your Honor.
反对有效
Sustained.
米勒女士  你发过誓你所说皆是事实
Miss Miller, you are under oath to tell the truth.
八月十七日晚她给你打过电话吗
Did she call you the night of August 17th?
打了
Uh... Yes.
你们说了什么
What did you talk about?
商量怎么给流浪汉提供食物
How we were gonna feed the homeless.
她具体说了些什么
What exactly did she say?
只是说她对此很兴奋  然后
Just that she was excited about it, and...
我们聊了一会儿她儿子  马尔科姆
we talked about her son, Malcolm, for a while.
你们聊了多久
How long did you speak?
大概十五分钟
About 15 minutes.
那好吧
Okay. Well...
电话记录显示
the, uh, phone record shows that
你们的通话时间少于两分钟
the two of you talked for less than two minutes.
是这样吗
Is that about right?
反对
Objection!
反对理由
On what grounds?
上述通话记录并未作为呈堂证供
This particular phone record was not in discovery.
请上前
Approach.
法官大人  辩方并未被告知有此通话记录
Your Honor, the defense was not given this phone record.
法官大人  如果你详细查看文件清单
Your Honor, if you look at the list of documents,
该通话记录在清单上
it's on discovery.
但是  法官大人  我们并不知道
But, Your Honor, we did not get this in discovery,
该通话记录的存在  也没有时间查证
this particular phone record, nor have we had the time to.
这上面说此记录数月前就已提供给你们
It says here that they were given months ago.
我三周前才接手此案件
Well, I was just given this case three weeks ago, and there was--
法官大人  我们不应为
Your Honor, we can't be held responsible
布莱恩特女士的无能承担责任
for Miss Bryant's incompetence here.
她早已拿到记录
She had them.
你继续
You may continue.
谢谢  法官大人
Thank you, Your Honor.
但是  法官大人  如果我们能
But, Your Honor, if we can...
请遵守审判规则  布莱恩特女士
Welcome to trial, Mrs. Bryant.
请立即回到你的座位
Now, step away.
好的
Okay.
我说到哪里了
Where was I?
通话记录
Phone records.
根据记录显示
Now, they show...
你们的通话不到两分钟  对吗
that you spoke for less than two minutes, right?
我确实记不清了
I-I really don't remember.
时间太久了
It's been so long ago.
或许你还记得通话之后你做了什么
Well, maybe you remember what you did after the call.
你做什么了吗
What did you do?
很晚了  我去睡了
Well, it was late, so I went to bed.
那么为什么在几分钟后
Well, then why was your cell phone used
葛蕾丝家附近的信号塔
and pinged to a cell tower
收到了你使用手机的数据信息
near Grace's home a few moments later?
我不记得了
I-I... I don't recall.
她的电话记录显示有你的来电
Her phone records show an incoming call from you.
你给她打过电话吗
Did you call her?
米勒女士  在先前的证词中你明确表示
Miss Miller, you made it very clear earlier in your testimony
你们是好朋友
that you two are friends.
我明白你十分关心她
I understand, you care for her deeply.
-你是不是在包庇她  -我没有
- Are you covering for her now? - No.
那你能解释这些通话记录吗
Then can you please clear up these phone records?
她住在罗特维尔县  这地方很偏远
She lives in Rotwell County. It's very rural.
她给你打了一个电话  你打给她两次
She called you once, you called her twice.
为什么
Why?
-我记不清了  -通话记录上都有
- I don't remember. - It's on the phone records.
她打给你  你们说了不到两分钟
She called you, you spoke for less than two minutes.
然后你去了她家  又打给她
Then you went to her house, you called her,
然后你回到了你家
then you were at your house.
你四十五分钟后再次打给她  这是怎么回事
You called her again 45 minutes later. Why?
我记不清了
I don't remember.
米勒女士  你可知道
Miss Miller, do you understand
你会因伪证罪被判入狱吗
that you can be put in jail for perjury?
你知道什么是伪证罪吧
You do know what perjury is, right?
非公勿入
法官大人
Your Honor...
证人请回答
The witness will answer.
她告诉我她杀死了他
She told me that she killed him.
葛蕾丝  我很抱歉
I'm sorry, Grace.
我没有其他问题了
No further questions.
布莱恩特女士  你还要问的吗
Mrs. Bryant, your witness.
没有其他问题  法官大人
No further questions, Your Honor.
好的
Okay.
你可以下去了
You may step down.
布莱恩特女士  辩方是否终止辩诉
Is the defense resting, Mrs. Bryant?
辩方请求终止
The defense rests.
控辩于上午九点终止
Closing arguments in the morning at 9:00 a.M.
现在休庭
We're adjourned.
全体起立
All rise.
你尽力了
You tried.
你怎么能忽视通话记录呢
How could you miss the phone records?
我
I,
我没看到  先生
I didn't see them, sir.
我
I,
我以为我看到了  但其实没有
I thought I saw them, but I didn't-- I didn't see them,
我完全乱了阵脚
and I was just completely overwhelmed.
-我  -自乱阵脚
- I... - Overwhelmed.
你没看见吗  我可看见了
You didn't see 'em? I saw 'em.
因为我一直在跟进此事  我一直在观察
'Cause I was shadowing you. I was watching it all along.
我不明白  我从业二十五年了
I don't get it. I... ...I just sit in that office for 25 years,
看着你种小年轻入行  又跳槽去私人律所
watching people like you come in, then go out to private practice,
去别的大公司  挣大钱
go to other firms, make more money,
但我都尊重  我受不了的是你高冷的姿态
but I respect it. I'm insulted by your callous demeanor.
你知道你刚刚做了什么吗
You know what you just did?
这是最起码的  你竟让证人在离开证人席时
This is 101. You let a witness leave the stand
说你的当事人是杀人犯
saying that your client was a murderer.
瞧瞧你干的好事
That's what you did.
他们整晚都会想这个
That's what they're gonna think about all night long.
我真不明白
I don't get it.
这种失误难得一见  我真是想不通
I guess it's a millennial thing. I'll never understand it.
亲爱的  来吧  吃一点
Baby, come on, just eat a little bit.
吃点吧  求你
Please, come on.
我不想吃  你是我爸吗  我不想吃
I don't want it! Who are you, my father? I don't want it!
对不起
I'm sorry.
行了吧
Okay?
我现在压力太大了
I'm just really stressed right now,
我知道你很生气
and I know you're upset,
但你听到他是怎么对我说话的了
but you heard the way he talked to me.
你为什么不帮我说话呢
Why didn't you say something?
因为我觉得他说的很有道理
'Cause he made a lot of good points.
虽然我不喜欢他的说话方式
I don't like the way he said it,
但他说的都是真话  茉莉
but he was telling you the truth, Jasmine.
忠言往往逆耳
The truth hurts sometimes.
真不敢相信你站在他那边
I can't believe you're taking his side.
亲爱的  我不是他那边的
I'm not on his side, baby.
我是你这边的  我是我们这边的
I'm on your side, I'm on our side.
我是会让你变得更好的那一边的
I'm on whatever's going to make you better.
忠言很难入耳
Truth is hard to get,
但如果你能入耳  它会让你变强大
but it can make you strong if you just let it.
-你就是个混蛋  -我不是
- You are such an ass. - I'm not the ass.
-你真混蛋  -我不是
- You are such an ass! - I'm not the ass.
-我绝不会弃你于危难而不顾  -真的吗
- I don't walk away when things get hard. - Are you serious?
-我非常认真  -真的吗
- Yeah, I'm dead serious. - Really?
茉莉  你不能永远躲在协议认罪的
You can't keep running away your whole life
案子后面逃避一辈子
hiding behind plea deals, Jasmine.
我在努力  这就是我为这个案子辩护的原因
I was trying! That's the reason why I'm trying this case.
好吧  有人说了几句打击你的话
Okay, so somebody says something that sets you back,
你就放弃了  宝贝
and you just walk away, babe.
-这案子输了  -不  还没有
- The case is lost! - No, it's not.
你看到陪审团的态度了
You saw the jury!
我该怎么办
What am I supposed to do?
你要做好你的本职工作  亲爱的
You're supposed to do your job, babe!
坚持到底
Till the end!
真的  你天生就该干这一行
I'm serious, the job you were born to do. That's...
亲爱的
Baby.
审判之初我看到了你眼中的激情
I saw the fire in your eyes when you started this case,
出现失误后  你的激情一下就没了
and I saw it just go away as soon as this moment happened.
把激情找回来
Just find it again.
结束了
It's done.
案子已经结束了
The case is closed.
剩下的就只是结案陈词了
All that's left is the closing argument.
我无能为力了
There's nothing I can do.
那你最好准备一篇精彩的结案陈词
Well, you better write one hell of a closing argument.
我好累
I'm tired.
宝贝
Babe.
你们已经听过不下四十五名证人的证词
You've heard the testimony of over 45 witnesses
所有证词都证明她有罪
that have attested to her guilt.
她最好的朋友指证她亲口承认了谋杀了他
Her own best friend said she told her that she killed him.
她比谁都了解她
She knew her better than anyone.
沃特斯女士杀害了香农·德隆
Miss Waters killed Shannon Delong,
并把他的尸体拖到乡下的沼泽地里
and she dragged his body out to a swamp in the country,
尸体因此失踪
never to be found again.
犯案手法十分残忍
That's cold-blooded.
犯案过程精心设计
That is calculated.
这是一起有预谋的谋杀
That is premeditated murder.
请将她绳之以法
And it's your job to bring her to justice.
你们有责任判她有罪
It is your job to find her guilty,
我们完全信任你们
and we have the utmost faith in you,
信任司法体制  你们会做出正确判断
and our legal system, that you will.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
布莱恩特女士
Mrs. Bryant?
Mrs. Bryant.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
辩方传唤萨拉·米勒出庭
The defense calls Sarah Miller.
法官大人  控辩双方均于昨日同意终止
Your Honor, both sides rested yesterday.
请上前来
Approach the bench.
法官大人  双方均终止了控辩
Your Honor, both sides rested.
我知道这律师是个新手  但这太荒唐了
I understand the counsel is a novice here. This is ridiculous.
等等  检察官  布莱恩特女士
Hold on, Counsel. Mrs. Bryant,
你清楚双方都终止控辩了吧
you do understand that both sides have rested?
我清楚  法官大人
Yes, I do, Your Honor,
但我想请米勒女士重新上证人席
but I would like to recall Miss Miller to the stand.
有何缘由
On what grounds?
她陈述后  我本应对她进行提问
I should have questioned her after she said what she said,
我不应终止辩论
and I should not have rested,
我想重新提问她  因为
and I would like to question her again because--
这不符合规矩
That's not how this works.
终止控辩后  你就不能再传唤证人了
Once you rest, you cannot call a witness.
如有异议  可提起上诉
Just take it up in appeal.
现在请做结案陈词
Closing arguments right now.
但是  法官大人  如果我能
But, Your Honor, if I could just...
退回去  陈词吧
Step back and argue.
现在就去  律师
Now, Counselor.
-辩方传唤萨拉·米勒  -法官大人
- The defense calls Sarah Miller. - Your Honor...
布莱恩特女士  对此我已作出裁决了
Mrs. Bryant, I have already ruled on that,
我不能再容忍
and I will not tolerate any more--
米勒女士  到证人席上去
Take the stand, Miss Miller.
-去证人席  -布莱恩特女士
- Take the stand. - Mrs. Bryant!
米勒女士  坐回去
Miss Miller, sit back down.
你不许上证人席
You are not taking the stand.
两位律师  请去我的办公室
Counselors, in my chambers now.
我不会去您的办公室  除非米勒女士
I will not be going to Your Honor's chambers until Miss Miller
-上证人席  -对此我已有裁决
- takes the stand. - I have ruled on the matter,
你必须到我的办公室来
and you will come to my chambers.
米勒女士不上证人席
I'm not going into Your Honor's chambers
我就不去您的办公室
until Miss Miller takes the stand.
米勒女士  请上证人席
Miss Miller, take the stand, please.
布莱恩特女士  如果你现在不来我的办公室
Mrs. Bryant, if you do not come into my chambers right now,
我将以藐视法庭罪拘捕你
I will hold you in contempt.
辩方请萨拉·米勒上证人席
The defense calls Sarah Miller to the stand.
法警
Bailiff.
你能相信吗
Can you believe this?
你究竟在搞什么名堂
So what the hell was that?
你在乎吗
The hell do you care?
反正我被炒了
I'm fired anyway.
那倒是  所以你自暴自弃了吗
Yeah, that's true. So you throw your life away anyway?
这不正是你想要的吗
That's what you wanted, isn't it?
我想要什么了
What I wanted?
-不是的  -如果这就是代价的话
- No. - And if that's what it takes.
她不该进监狱
She shouldn't go to jail.
这不公平
This is unfair.
不公平  不公平  就是这个词
Unfair, unfair. That's the word.
现在你懂了吧
Now you get it.
一切都是不公平的  法律也不可能公平
All of this is unfair. The law can be unfair,
而你的职责就是走进法庭  让它公平
but it was your job to walk into that courtroom and make it fair.
但恰恰相反  你做了什么
But instead, what'd you do?
你在说服这个女人不接受认罪协议后
Go to court half-assed after you convinced this woman
就半途而废了吗
to not take a great plea deal?
瞧瞧吧  就是这么不公平
Now look, it's all unfair.
听着  我很喜欢你现在的这种个人信念
Listen, I love this personal conviction that you got going on
但现在时机不对
right now, but it's on the wrong side of time.
你不道歉  法官是不会放你出来的
The judge is gonna make you sit here until you apologize.
你觉得这很了不起  他让我们休庭
You think that's something, he gave us a recess
好让我们替你做结案陈词
so that we can do your closing arguments.
唐尼激动坏了
Donnie is thrilled.
你不会被判无效辩护  你到底在想什么
You weren't gonna get a mistrial. What the hell were you thinking?
在这里好好享受吧
Enjoy your time here.
喂  罗里
Hey, Rory.
怎么
Yeah?
去你妈的
Fuck you.
狱中激情
Passion behind bars.
真不错
Nice.
陪审团一致认为
We, the jury,
被告人葛蕾丝·沃特斯
find Grace Waters, the defendant,
被弗吉尼亚州指控犯有谋杀罪
guilty of murder as charged by the state of Virginia.
我没事  亲爱的
I'm all right, baby.
我没事
I'm all right.
-没事的  萨拉
- It's okay - Sarah.
-没事的  我来照顾他  -谢谢
- It's okay, I got him. - Thank you.
没事的
It's all right.
这是一个乌佐吗
Is that an Uzo?
在非洲买的  很特别吧
Got this in Africa. One of a kind.
我照顾他  没事的
I got him. It's okay.
你绝对不会相信你的摄影师做了什么
You will not believe what your photographer did.
需要我开车送你去吗
Do you need me to drive you?
因为你要去
'Cause you are going.
警卫
Guard!
你想在你朋友面前和我吵架吗
You want to talk to me like that in front of your friend?
她的朋友
Her friend.
警卫
Guard!
我要给我的律师打电话
I need to call my lawyer.
陪审团裁决葛蕾丝·沃特斯有罪
The verdict in the Grace Waters case is guilty.
判决将在数月内执行
Sentencing is scheduled in just a few months.
对于今天在法庭的人或陪审员来说
This turn of events is no shock to anybody
事态的转变并不令人意外
who was in the courtroom today or the jurors.
这是意料之中的
This was what was expected.
葛蕾丝被定罪是预料之中的事
Grace was expected to be convicted,
并没有什么变化
and nothing changed here today.
预计正在准备认罪协议
...predict that some sort of plea deal is in the works.
亲爱的  向法官道歉吧
Baby, tell the judge that you're sorry
这样我们才能回家  求你了
so we can go home, please.
天气预报称
Looking at our forecast,
下午将有场大雨
we have a bunch of rain coming this afternoon.
这个季节我们从未有过异常高的降雨量
This season, we haven't had abnormally high amounts of rain...
你还好吗
You okay?
还好
Yeah.
我没事
Yeah, I'm okay.
宝贝  你确定今天要去见萨拉吗
You sure you want to see Sarah today, babe?
只是...
It's just...
是的  我该去
Yeah, I should.
你知道
You know.
我知道她现在的感觉和我一样糟
I know she's feeling just as bad as I am right now.
-亲爱的就在这里停吧  -现在吗
- Babe, just pull over right here. - Right now?
对  我走过去
Yeah. I can walk the rest of the way.
-你确定吗  -是的
- You sure? - Yeah.
你该回去上班了
And you gotta get back to work.
你确定吗  亲爱的
You sure, babe?
就要下雨了
It's about to rain.
没事的
No, I'll be fine.
好吧  我爱你
Okay. Love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
-注意安全  -我会的
- Be safe, all right? - I will.
-再见  -再见  宝贝
- Bye. - Bye, baby.
-我们回家见  -好
- I'll see you at home. - All right.
你好
Hi.
你好  我认识你
Hi, I know you.
你要去哪里
Hey, where are you going?
我该走了
I gotta go.
不  不  来吧
No, no, no. Come on, come on.
-你要去哪里  -我得离开
- Where are you going? - I gotta get away!
好吧  我们回萨拉女士的家
Oh, okay, let's go back to Miss Sarah's house.
来吧  没事的  她知道你出来了吗
Come on, it's okay. Does she know you're out here?
她今天去银行了  今天是一号  再见
She go to the bank today. It's the first. Bye.
好吧   我们回萨拉女士家
Okay. Well, let's-- let's go back to Miss Sarah's house.
没事的  她可能甚至不知道你出来了
It's all right. She probably doesn't even know you're out here.
-走吧  下雨了我们回去  -不要
- Let's go. Let's get you out this rain. - No.
不  别逼我回去  求求你不要
No, don't... don't make me go back there. Please don't.
-来吧  没事的  我帮你  -不要
- Come on, it's okay. It's okay. I got you. - No.
-现在有我陪着你  -我要回我家
- You're with me now. - I want to go to my house.
我家
My house.
你家吗
Your house?
来吧  没事  我陪你
Come on. It's okay. I got you.
-我们进去  -别逼我再回去
-Let's go in to get some. - Don't make me go in no more.
我再也不想待在那里了
I don't want to stay there no more.
别逼我再回去  求你了  不要
Don't make me go back there. Please don't.
来吧
Come on.
你现在安全了
You're safe now.
你走的时候没关门
You left the door wide open.
我没钥匙
Well, I don't have all the keys.
没有钥匙  好吧
All the keys? Oh, okay.
进来吧
Just come on in.
这是萨拉女士的家  你就住在这里
You're at Miss Sarah's house. This is where you live.
-这你的家  没事的  -不  不是
- This is your house, it's okay. - No, no. No.
我  我要回我自己家
I... I want to go to m-my own house.
我  我的房子在
My... my house is... is...
没事
It's all right.
我给你倒点水  好吗
Let me get you some water, okay?
我的房子在西卡摩街2989号
My house is two... 2989 Sycamore Street.
-西卡摩街吗  -对
- Sycamore Street? - Yeah.
那才是我住的地方
That's where I live.
地址是西卡摩街2989号
The address is 2989 Sycamore Street.
西卡摩街2989号
2989 Sycamore Street.
我不想死在这里
I don't wanna die here like...
就像葛瑞安  本达和珊娜那样
Gloria, and... and... Brenda, and... and Shane.
珊娜从房顶跳了下去
Shane jumped off the roof.
从房顶跳了下去  亲爱的
Jumped off the roof, dear.
我什么都没了  都没了
I have nothing! Nothing!
不
No!
她是一名摄影师
She was a photographer.
非常有天份
And so, so talented.
我的天啊
Oh, my God. Is, um...
这是珊娜的作品吗
Is this... is this Shane's work?
是的  没错
Yes, yes. Yes.
没有什么比
Seeing the world
通过相机镜头来看这个世界更棒的事了
through the eyes of a 35-millimeter, there's nothing like that.
有人进了我的账户
Somebody got into my accounts.
他们有我的密码
They got my passwords.
我要回我自己的家
You know, I-I was gonna go to my house
报警  这样警察就能来帮我们了
and call the police so they could come and help us.
我得先自保
I had to build my own boat first.
这难道不对吗
Ain't that a fact?
我帮不了所有的人
I mean, I can't help everybody.
他们都很饿
They're hungry.
好的
Okay.
你待在这里
You stay here.
待在这里  我一会就回  好吗
Stay here. I'll be right back, okay?
就待在这里
Stay right here.
-你有权保持沉默  -布莱恩特警官
- You have the right to remain silent. - Officer Bryant?
布莱恩特收到  请讲沃特
Go for Bryant. Come back, Walt.
你不会相信这个的  看看你的电脑
You won't believe this. Check your computer.
待在这里别动
Stay right here. Don't move.
该死
Oh, shit!
救救我  救救我
Help me. Help me.
你好  爱丽丝
Hello, Alice.
不是我放她进来的
I... I didn't let her in.
求求你别伤害我
Please don't hurt me.
你抓住她了吗
You got her?
有些人永远不会吸取教训
Some people never learn.
是吗
Do they?
我妈妈在和你说话
My mama's talking to you.
但他们得会学会管好自己的事
But they gonna learn to mind their own damn business.
警察  开门
Police, open up!
乔丹
Jordan!
警察  快开门
Police, open up!
我是布莱恩特警官  现在在西课巷2342号
This is Officer Bryant, location 2342 West Lesson Lane,
请求支援  警察  快开门
requesting backup. Police, open up!
支援将在七分钟内到达
We're seven minutes out.
-女士请开门  我是警察  -哪位
- Open up, ma'am, police. - Hello?
-快开门  -好的  你好
- Yes, open up. - All right. All right. Hello.
你好
Yes, hello.
我在找我的妻子
I'm looking for my wife.
你的妻子是谁
Who's your wife?
你知道她是谁  她叫茉莉·布莱恩特
You know who she is. Jasmine Bryant,
是你朋友葛蕾丝·沃特斯的代理律师
she was representing your friend Grace Waters?
-她说她要来这里看看  -我没见过她
- She said she was gonna come by here. - Well, I haven't seen her.
好吧  我可以进来吗
Okay, well, you mind if I come in?
你有搜查证吗
Do you have a warrant?
你没有的话你不能进来
If you don't have a warrant, you can't come in.
我说过了  她不在这里
I told you, she's not here.
她不在这里
She's not here.
天啊
Jesus.
茉莉
Jasmine!
我的妻子在哪里
Where's my wife?
茉莉
Jasmine!
不  不要
No, no.
好的  别动
Okay, don't move.
别动
Don't move.
待在这里
Stay right here.
茉莉
Jasmine!
Jasmine?
茉莉
Jasmine!
亲爱的
Oh, baby.
住手
Stop!
茉莉  把枪给我  来
Jasmine, give it to me. Here.
我觉得他死了  他已经死了
I think he's done. He's done.
我们发现香农·德隆的
What we've learned is that Shannon Delong,
真名为马修斯 米勒斯
whose real name is Maurice Mills,
他与其母巴蒂·米勒斯也就是萨拉·米勒
and his mother, Betty Mills, also known as Sarah Miller,
一直以来绑架老年女性
have been kidnapping elderly women,
侵占她们的财产
taking their wealth
并为占有她们的社保而扣押她们
and holding them hostage for their social security.
目前他因重婚罪  诈骗罪等多种罪名
Now he's wanted in nine states for bigamy
在九个州被通缉
and several other crimes, including racketeering.
此外我们还发现
And we've also discovered
此二人不仅扣押老年女性作为人质
that not only were these two holding the elderly women hostage,
据我们证实  其子在其他各州
but he's wanted in several states
还因诈骗至少十六名中年女性而被通缉
for conning at least 16 middle-aged women that we can verify.
这对母子从事该项犯罪活动已超过二十五年
Now, the mother-and-son duo have been at this for over 25 years,
在此期间  从受害者处掠夺了大量财产
stealing millions from their victims over this time period.
葛蕾丝·沃特斯是其中一名受害者
Grace Waters was one of the victims.
根据我们收到的最新证据
In light of the new evidence we received,
弗吉尼亚州希望向沃特斯女士道歉
the state of Virginia wishes to apologize to Miss Waters,
你无罪释放
and you are free to go.
我们仍在努力调查
We are working on finding out what happened
这些妇女到底经历了什么
to the fortunes of these women.
葛蕾丝·沃特斯的公开辩护人
Grace Waters' public defender,
茉莉·布莱恩特是揭露整个事件的导火索
Jasmine Bryant, is the reason this entire scheme was uncovered.
-沃特斯女士  -他们出来了
- Miss Waters - Here they come. Here they come.
-好了 -沃特斯女士
- Okay. - Miss Waters.
沃特斯女士  无罪释放后的感觉如何
Miss Waters, how does it feel to be free?
太好了
Wonderful.
沃特斯女士  事情结束了你高兴吗
Miss Waters, are you glad it's over?
事情没有结束
It ain't over.
借过一下
Excuse me.
如今萨拉·米勒或者说巴蒂·米勒斯仍然在逃
At present, Sarah Miller, rather, Betty Mills, is still on the run.
你在照顾老年人方面有什么经验吗
So what kind of experience do you have working with the elderly?
我照顾他们
I take care of them.
我爱他们
And I love them
就好像他们是我的家人一样
just like they're my own family.
来吧  来见见我妈
Well, come, I want you to meet my mother.
好的
I'd like that.
她叫什么名字来着
What's her name again?
-露安  -露安
- LuAnn. - LuAnn.
我好像听过这个名字
Oh, I think I read about her.
她是不是在某个金融机构工作过
Didn't she work with some financial institution?
对  确实是
Oh, yeah, she did.
她当时的职位是什么来着
What was her position again?
-她当过十年的经理  -天呐
- She was a manager for ten years. - Oh, my.
令人印象深刻
Impressive.